Dude, you lie to my face one more [beep]
time, I'll sue you.
Okay, I'm ready.
Some people go through life never hearing the
word no and it shows.
It's- it's the dog.
Property, you are going to go to jail.
They grow up into full-blown Karens,
convinced the world revolves around them.
So I'm gonna call my family.
Well, no, you're not, you're not going
anywhere right now.
Yeah. Yeah.
Put your hands behind your back.
Hell, no. Hell, no. Hell, no.
I was going outside to get my card. [crying]
Turn around and face the wall.
Today, Detective Dale will take us through
five cases where Karens turned arrests into
felonies.
As law enforcement, some of my worst
experiences have been with entitled Karens
who are absolutely convinced they're
incapable of doing anything wrong.
Entitlement really is nature's finest
blindfold, thicker than a nightshift worker's
blackout curtains, because here we have a
woman somehow blaming other cars for her
crime. What I see in your eyes indicate to me
that you have been consuming alcohol.
That's funny because you guys haven't done
anything of that nature to anybody else who's
been hit.
Officers were dispatched to a scene where a
car had been rear-ended a stop sign.
When they arrived, they were met by a woman
who immediately blamed other drivers for the
incident. She also demanded that those
drivers take a breathalyzer test while
refusing to cooperate herself.
Hey, can I talk to you down here, please?
Okay. Thank you so much. Okay.
Are these all your, are these all your bags?
Yes.
Oh, okay. We're just gonna go right here.
Okay.
Hey, um, I know you told your story to those
officers already.
Would you mind telling me again what, what
you remember happening?
I literally was at the, the stop sign right
here and got rear-ended. I was about to make
a left. So you were stopped in traffic, like,
gonna make a left here-
Yeah
... on this street?
Slammed into me.
Okay. Do you know which car hit you?
The car, like, I don't know what, uh... The
car in front here. Not this Kia.
The one in front.
The car in front of it?
Yeah.
Okay. And are you injured at all?
I don't... I feel like I'm, you know, like
just...
You think you're worked up?
Yeah.
Maybe?
Were you wearing your seatbelt?
I don't know. Yes, of course.
And did your airbags go off?
No.
Okay.
But I, I just... I don't know yet, but I'm, I
am shooken up and I
don't know.
Yeah. Well, at least you don't have any
physical injuries.
No, yeah.
I mean, you may, you may experience some pain
later, 'cause usually, you know, the shock of
a, an accident, maybe like tomorrow you might
feel some type of-
And I've been in a wreck before that's been
my fault and shattered my arm with my airbag.
So I kinda know that feeling, but-
Yeah
... I feel like I'm just so angry right now,
because like I'm, I'm very grateful that
everybody's okay. But God forbid like a child
in the car or a baby, like-
Yeah
... I just don't know. And I'm just-
No, I totally understand. Yeah.
So-
Did the fire department look at you when they
came out?
No, I d- I didn't sign anything.
Okay. You didn't need them to... You felt you
didn't need them to look at you or anything?
No, they didn't offer it either.
Okay.
So...
Okay. You don't feel you need to be checked
by them right now?
Not right now, no. I can't promise within the
next 24 hours I might feel that way, but
right now, no. I can't promise within the
right now, no. I can't promise within the nex
t 24 hours I might feel that way, but right
now, no. I can't promise within the nex t 24
hours I might feel that way, but right now,
no. I can't promise within the nex t 24 hours
I might feel that way, but right now, no. I
can't promise within the nex t 24 hours I
might feel that way, but right now, no. I
might feel that way, but right now, no. I can
't promise within the nex t 24 hours I might
feel that way, but right now, no. I can't
promise within the nex t 24 hours I might
promise within the nex t 24 hours I might fee
l that way, but right now, no. I can't
promise within the nex t 24 hours I might
feel that way, but right now, no. I can't
feel that way, but right now, no. I can't pro
mise within the nex t 24 hours I might feel
that way, but right now, no. I can't promise
within the nex t 24 hours I might feel that
way, but right now, no. I can't promise
within the nex t 24 hours I might feel that w
ay, but right now, no. I can't promise within
the nex t 24 hours I might feel that way, but
right now, no. I can't promise within the nex
t 24 hours I might feel that way, but right
now, no. I can't promise within the nex t 24
hours I might feel that way, but right now,
no. I can't promise within the nex t 24 hours
I might feel that way, but right now, no. I
can't promise within the nex t 24 hours I
might feel that way, but right now, no. I
can't promise within the nex t 24 hours I mig
ht feel that way, but right now, no. I can't
promise within the nex t 24 hours I might
feel that way, but right now, no. I can't
feel that way, but right now, no. I can't pro
mise within the nex t 24 hours I might feel
that way, but right now, no. I can 't promise
within the nex t 24 hours I might feel that
way, but right now, no. I can 't promise
within the nex t 24 hours I might feel that w
ay, but right now, no. I can 't promise
within the nex t 24 hours I might feel that
way, but right now I feel okay. Yeah, true.
That, that's different. You can always go see
your own doctor too. Right. Yeah. Or go to
the emergency room or whatever. Did he take a
breathalyzer? Who's that? The, the... I mean,
in my opinion, the driver that caused this.
No. Well, so let me explain something to you.
Fir- first, um, with DUIs in the State of
Florida, um, we can't immediately administer
a breathalyzer to somebody. We have to
actually conduct an investigation beforehand.
Okay, so the officers that have, um, done
this traffic crash investigation, um, are
done with the investigation and they've
called me. I'm a DUI investigator, and
they're concerned maybe you have been
drinking tonight, okay? Well, can't we just
do a breathalyzer? Well, like I said just a
minute ago, it's, it's... That's not how it
works in Florida. Oh. We actually have to do
the investigation to determine whether or not
you were impaired first. Okay, but I honestly
feel like I... That's because I gave them a
hard time, so... And you know what, and if
that's the case, then you didn't give me a
hard time, so there, we, I don't have any ill
feelings about it. Okay. You know what I
mean? Like, it's not- I mean, I ju- I, I'm, I
feel very passionately about this and I would
never make... I just, I feel like I would
never make that decision. I did have a- Yeah.
I just, I feel like I would never make that
decision. I did have a- Yeah. I drank with my
coworker at 5:00 PM, but that was the last
drink I had. And I made a conscious effort-
So at, at five was the last time you had a
drink? ... at five. Yes. And how many drinks
did you have? Um... Two sangrias. Okay. And
that was it. And then we went shopping in
Hyde Park. Okay. And I was on my way home.
Okay. Okay. Um, the law tells me I have to
read you your rights. Okay. And I know for
some people that seems scary. The Miranda
rights? Go ahead. But it's, but it's not,
because it doesn't mean you're under arrest.
Right. Okay. There's a lot of like, "Oh, I
saw this on TV and this means I'm under
arrest." Not true. Okay. You're not under
arrest. Okay. Are you willing to answer
questions or make a statement without an
attorney being present? Uh, I don't know.
Listen, you can decide as you go if you want.
Okay.
I mean, you don't have to tell me yes or no
now. It's uh, totally up to you.
I'm trying to be as cooperative as possible,
but if I am injured, I don't want to...
I totally understand.
Okay.
I totally understand. And I tell you what,
even to make you feel a little bit more
comfortable, I won't even ask you any
questions, okay? Just to circumvent this
whole you're making a statement thing, okay?
But what I would like to do is just take a
look at your eye, check your eyes. Sure.
Okay? Um, now you already told me you're not,
you, you don't have any physical injuries.
You don't feel like you're severely injured
right now. Do you have any medical problems?
Taken any medications for anything?
Um, I take, I take antidepressants. I'm on
birth control. I'm on Adderall.
Any problems with your eyes?
No. I should wear glasses at night, but I'm
getting my prescription renewed, so...
If you're trying to quietly get away with a
crime, your best bet is to keep quiet.
Unless, of course, you want them to catch a
whiff of the sangria fumes leaking from your
pores. When the officer asked her to take a
field sobriety test, her reaction said it
all.
Okay. I'm actually gonna have you stand right
over here and look at me this way, 'cause I
don't want you looking at traffic. Um, can
you put your feet together and then arms
straight down to your side? Now, I have to
shine a light towards your, towards your eyes
while I do this. I'm gonna try not gonna um,
I'm gonna try not to blind you. Can you move
your hair back? Yeah.
All right. You see the red light here?
What I want you to do is follow that red
light with your eyes, but keep your head
still. Okay, now I'm gonna move it back and
forth quite a few times. This, this takes a
little while to do. If you have to blink,
that, that's totally fine. You can blink,
okay? But just focus on the red light. Okay.
All right. Do, um, do you have other shoes in
the red light. Okay. All right. Do, um, do
you have other shoes in the vehicle with you
or are those the only shoes that you have?
These are the only shoes I have. Okay.
There's a couple other exercises that I wanna
ask you to do, okay?
Uh, it's, it's, it's all part of the
standardized field sobriety exercises, okay?
I just feel like I'm so nervous right now....
this, uh, I feel like-
Right
... I didn't even cause this, and I'm the
one, like under scrutiny.
[siren wailing]
And you know what? And, and, and that may be
the case even if you didn't cause it.
Um,
I, I feel where you're coming from
and I'm sorry you feel nervous. Whatever I
can do to help alleviate that, I will.
Um, but I do wanna to ask you to de- you
know, I would like you to perform the, the
exercises. Um, those are pretty big heels so,
um,
I'll give you the option. You can, if you
feel very, very comfortable walking in those,
you the option. You can, if you feel very,
very comfortable walking in those, you can
listen to my instructions and decide whether
or not- No, because I feel like that's-
... you want to do it with or without them
on.
I just, can I, like do I have to do this
right now?
You like our videos? Don't forget to
subscribe.
Well, there's no penalty for refusing them.
But I have to tell you, if you refuse to do
the field sobriety exercises, you force me to
make a decision either to arrest you or not
arrest you, based on what I've seen so far.
Okay. I want to talk to my family. [sniffs]
Well, making a phone call right now is not an
option, okay? This is... You're an adult.
This is a decision that you have to make.
No.
I will, I will talk to you and explain
everything to you that you want to know-
This-
... as far as the law is concerned.
That's... I didn't cause this.
Well, that doesn't matter. And the, it-
It does because I feel like I'm being, I'm
being put in a position right now to
prove something that I didn't, I didn't
create.
Well, I'm not saying that you, you caused the
accident at all. Th- I'm not saying that.
I'm not accusing you of causing the accident,
no.
And you're not-
But-
... letting me call my family and ask-
... them what I should do right now?
But listen-
With or without a lawyer present?
Listen, listen to what, listen to what I'm s-
I'm asking no. Yes or no?
Yeah, I don't want you to call your family
right now, no.
Why?
No. Because I'm in the middle of an
investigation, okay?
But-
And you're an adult. You can make your own
decisions, okay?
Yeah, I don't care. I'm, I'm telling you
what's gonna accommodate my needs to make me
feel most comfortable.
Well, unfortunately, that's not an option
right now.
Okay, let me explain to you again where I'm
coming from, okay?
And, and, uh, this is, this is my
observations on you so far, is, uh, I can
smell alcohol.
Um, you have watery, bloodshot eyes.
You're-
Yeah, because I'm about to start crying.
[traffic rumbling]
Your speech is slurred, okay? And, and what I
see in your eyes indicate to me
that you have been consuming alcohol.
That's funny because you guys haven't done
anything of that nature to anybody else who's
been hit. I haven't seen you run a sobriety
test on me.
Well-
So I'm gonna call my family.
Well, no, you're not, you're not going
anywhere right now.
Yeah.
Okay? Come here.
No.
Put your hands behind your back.
No, no, no, no, stop. Why are you doing
that?
Put your hands-
Why are you doing that?
Stop her. Stop her.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch her.
Why are you doing that?
Get up, get up, get up.
Stop. Hey.
Stop. Stop.
Because I can't call my family.
Grab, grab her right arm. Grab her right arm.
Come on.
I can't call my family?
And hold that.
Grab her right arm.
I can't call my family? [handcuffs clinking]
Calm down. Calm down, please.
Where? I can't call my family?
Calm down. Calm down.
I'm calling for you. I'm coming for you.
Hey.
I can't call my family?
Come on, the... You're under arrest. [system
beeping] Will you grab, someone grab her
phone? Yes, I got it. I, it's here.
Why would you not let me call my family?
That's not an option right now.
Why? Why?
Because I said so.
Yeah, my brother's at ATF and he's been on
the phone the whole fucking time.
That's fine. [handcuffs clinking]
Yeah, it is fine. And you know what? What you
did was not fine.
You wouldn't let me call my family-
Okay
... and that's not okay.
Let me lock these cuffs before we get in.
Okay, good.
Good.
I didn't fucking do anything. This person who
caused this wreck.
This should be open.
Put your head... Okay, let me see.
Who got her, who's got her phone?
I got it.
This is all her stuff.
This is all her stuff? Because someone
stepped up to you.
She took something and she took like a... I
don't know what it was.
A large bottle of wine.
Some kind of liquid.
It was under... This is his air bag.
Large bottle of champagne.
Did she call for an ambulance? Yes. Yes.
How
come?
Because she was driving and we were looking
for the-
Ma'am, ma'am.
Hey guys, let's not, let's not argue about
it.
It doesn't-
No, no, we're not arguing.
She was driving.
Cause of the crash doesn't matter.
Shut the fuck up.
You fucking bum.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
That's enough. Get away, buddy.
We gonna go down there for a reason.
Time to leave.
Go ahead. No, you two go.
Hey, you're, you're, you're gonna end up...
Yes, ma'am. I'm talking to you. Yes, ma'am.
Sorry.
If she had
even the slightest clue how the law works,
she would have just taken
the sobriety test and walked off with a nice,
neat DUI.
Instead, she chose the scenic route to
disaster.
It wasn't until officers explained what
refusing a breath test actually meant that it
finally hit her how royally she'd messed up.
Just take a peek in there, see if you see any
like, containers or anything.
No, she said she dumped this cup right there.
She said she dumped this cup.
What cu- where's the cup?
The white cup over there. She said she dumped
it.
She dumped that out?
Okay, there's a pen, like a THC pen
right here as well.
It could explain her dilated pupils,
sure.
Right there.
See it?
Yeah.
It could be, I don't know. It could be vape.
Who knows?
Yeah.
And not... Just leave it. All right.
Hey, who was driving the silver Ford?
Oh, that's mine.
You were driving?
Um,
you injured at all?
Are you injured at all?
I don't know. I'm just really nervous. Like,
I just can't stop shaking.
Okay.
Did he FaceTime me or didn't FaceTime him?
Was she in the car with you?
No, this is my mom.
Was anybody in the car with you?
Um, it was two people were in the car with
me, but they left.
Were they injured at all?
Um, they weren't injured.
Okay.
Hey, hey.
Did he FaceTime me?
Thank you.
And do you know where her purse
is?
I took the, uh... No, he can have it. I to- I
took credit card out of it. Were you injured
at all? So I got a, uh, got a burn here.
Burn from this, uh, airbag?
Yeah.
Airbag burn? The seatbelt mark? Okay.
I got burned here.
My neck is a little bit hurt, but it's not a
big deal.
Just your neck?
Yeah.
Okay, we're out of here. Huh?
You got hers and his email?
I got hers. Yeah, we got it. We got
everything. We can go.
[door opening]
We're going down to the jail. I'm gonna ask
you to do a breath test. Are you willing to
do a breath test. Are you willing to do that?
No.
Okay. [system beeping] . Now I have to read
you something since you said you don't want
to read you something since you said you
don't want to take the breath test, okay? It
involves what happens to your driver's
license. I'm Officer ******.
... department. I am now requesting that you
submit to a lawful test of your breath, for
the purpose of determining its alcohol
content. Will you take the test I'm
requesting? No.
Okay. If you refuse to take the test I have
requested of you, your driving privilege will
be suspended for a period of one year for a
first refusal or 18 months [beeping] if your
driving privilege has been previously
suspended, or if you have been previously
fined under Florida Statute 327.35215, for
refusing to submit to a lawful test of your
breath, urine, or blood.
Do you understand what I've just read to you?
No, I want a lawyer present.
Okay, do you understand what I just read to
you?
No.
What do you not understand?
All of it. I want a lawyer present for all of
this.
I understand, and I'll- I'll get to that in
just a second.
But I-
No, I don't understand it. And I want a
lawyer present.
Well, explain to me what you don't
understand.
All of it, and I want a lawyer present, point
blank, period.
Okay, that's fine. And you'll be able to call
your lawyer here in a minute.
But I need to make sure you understand what I
just read to you.
No, I don't understand it, because I should
not be in the backseat of a car right now or
arrested for wanting to talk to a member of
my family.
That has nothing to do with you under-
I want my attorney.
That has nothing to do with you
understanding-
I want my attorney.
... has nothing to do with you understanding
what I just read.
I don't understand it.
Do you want me to read it again?
Nope.
I want an attorney present.
So what this is saying is if you refuse the
breath test, your license is going to be
suspended for one year.
Okay, and I'm gonna challenge that.
Do you understand that?
Nope.
You don't understand that your license is
gonna be suspended for one year?
Nope.
Why not?
Because I didn't do anything wrong.
Okay, th- that can be your defense, that's
fine. What I'm telling you is...
You're saying-
... what the law is.
You're not saying it's an, immediately, that
is what is
going to an effect. That is a chance that I'm
willing to take if I'm not taking...
Um, that's not how it works. What happens is
if you refuse the breath test, um, your
license gets [beeping] suspended immediately.
Why?
Because that's what the law is.
That's weird, 'cause, you know-
I didn't, I didn't make the law. I'm just
telling you what it is.
Yeah, I actually know the law though, and my
boyfriend, that didn't happen to him, so
that's fine.
So you understand it's going to be suspended
for a year if you don't take the breath test?
No, I'm not accepting that.
Why not?
And I want my attorney present, point blank,
period.
That's it.
Okay, let's step out.
Do you have everything on you? Anything on
you that can possibly stick to me, anything
like that? I got a patch up.
Yeah.
Nothing hidden in your bra, nothing like
that?
All right.
Hold on, I just need to go that way.
She was charged with DUI and resisting
arrest.
As entitled as this woman was, she was still
sober enough to navigate the situation.
Our next suspect, yeah, she needed a sitter.
Whoa!
Why are you taking me to jail?
Entitlement is a sickness. And when you mix
it with alcohol and a warped sense of
superiority, it turns into a full-blown
disaster, not just for the culprit,
but for the poor cops caught in the
crossfire.
Why is it on your vest?
Because I took your ID to run you.
Because you like me. Honey, I'll never do
you.
You got a -ing kid on the top of your head.
That's a bad spot.
On December 25th, 2023, officers were called
to a hotel
after a woman refused to leave her room well
past checkout.
When they knocked, she ignored them
completely, refusing to open the door.
And when she finally did speak up, the
officers probably wished she hadn't.
Um, he was supposed to have been gone by
12:00, it's now 2:00.
Okay.
And he just called and was saying some very
inappropriate things to me.
Um, as far as I know, he's still in the room.
I don't know, but I'd like him to be gone.
Would you like him trespassed from the
property?
Yes.
Okay.
I mean...
You mind coming up with us?
Not today. Yeah, I can come down.
Okay.
What was he saying when he called?
Um, probably would've put a bag over my head.
He was gonna make me naked.
That's not very nice.
No.
Could you stand over here, please? [knocking]
Who do you want?
Police. Come to the door, please.
I can't.
Why can't you? Are you okay right now,
physically?
What?
Are you physically okay? Can you come to the
door, please?
What?
Can you come to the door, please?
No, I can't. Take it off.
Okay. Well, if you don't come to the door,
I'm going to open the door.
Hey, she'll kill you.
Well, where is your dog?
Right here. I put a leash on so she doesn't
tear up your flat, ass.
All right. Please do put a leash on the dog.
Are you black or white?
I don't see the relevance.
I do. My dog will lick you.
Okay.
Yes.
Is your dog on a leash now?
No, not yet.
I want you to open the door right now.
Well, why?
So that I can talk to you.
You can talk to me through the door. We'll go
in there.
If you don't open the door, I'm going to open
the door.
Whatever.
I'll just sit here, wait for you.
Don't you try to do anything. You got a key,
right?
I do. Come unlock the door, please.
Nope.
Please come unlock the door.
No. It's Christmas. You're scaring me,
mother-
Well, I'm sorry that you're afraid. I'm not
trying to scare you. Please come to the door.
You better go, or I'll call home.
Get your ass in front of this.
Where are you? I can't see you.
Where are you?
You ain't white.
I'm concerned.
Why?
Can you please open the door so I can talk to
you?
Hey.
Harold.
I know your name is Harold or something like
that.
Okay. My name is Corporal Harris, actually.
Harold.
Can you please unlock, open the door?
No. Merry Christmas. Leave me alone.
Okay, listen, if you don't open that door,
I'm going to come in there.
And when I come in there, I'm going to take
you to jail.
Okay. I'll wait for you. Why are you coming
to my room?
Whoa!
Why are you taking me to jail?
Jams 20b.
Hold on, baby. It's okay.
Hey, puppy. Hey, puppy.
Nope. Nope. She's my service dog. That's too
tight.
That's too tight.
I'm telling you, it's too tight.
I understand that.
Okay, then loosen it.
My fingers fit inside of it.
Hold on, loosen the fucking cuffs. Loosen
them or I'll fart all over you.
Okay, you're gonna have to pay for this,
brother. You know that, right?
What?
Harris. [police radio]
Corporal Harris, walk with me, please. We're
going over there.
Take your hand off. Take your fat hands off.
We're going over there to have a seat. Come
with me.
I can't 'cause you won't... How am I gonna
move?
Okay, I can bring you over there. You can
stand up and we can walk now.
How am I gonna move?
Come on.
Does this help? Stay here.
Come here. Don't touch that.
Hey, puppy. Have a seat, please.
Let me sit over here. Come here. Don't touch
my dog. It's the law. It's a federal fucking
law. It's a federal fucking law. Sit down,
please. Please sit down.
Don't you fuckin' touch my fucking dog.
Okay, is there a reason-
Ah, ah
... why you're still in here?
Billy, come here. Sit down. You fucking
bastard, don't sit down.
Where's your ID at?
It's on the bed you fucking pig. No.
Hey, puppy.
Sit down.
Keep her on, wait for a second.
Right now. Don't touch my dog.
Who are you?
Prince? You're a detective.
7:55 to base. Can you run a 27 for me?
Hello?
Tell me who was trespassing and why.
We asked you to go and you didn't.
Who asked me to go?
This is trafficking report.
Who... Lieutenant.
10-4 Florida.
Lieutenant, look at me, sir.
Who asked me to go?
I don't... Who asked me to leave?
The hotel, and then we came to talk to you
and you didn't want to talk to us.
No, I didn't want to talk to you. Of course,
it's Christmas. Why would I want to talk to
you? Yeah.
And the hotel did not. I just checked out.
If you checked out, why are you here?
Because... [laughs]
Uh, 'cause you guys came and fucking
handcuffed me.
Yeah.
I was leaving, so what's the problem?
Miss Umbarto, are you from here?
No. Well, do you think I'm from here? You saw
my license. What's the address, sir?
I did see your license. It's very common to
have licenses that are from other states.
And it's none of your business. My address is
what's on that fucking card.
All I'm trying to ask is 'cause I'm trying to
find out if somebody can come get your dog or
if somebody can come get your dog or if I'm
calling animal control. If you don't want to
work with me- You can't do that
... I'll call animal control.
You don't know the law.
I can do that.
Okay, whatever. Call the cops.
Yes, ma'am.
Get your fucking boss down here, brother.
This is my boss.
Then you know the law. You know you can't
take this dog from me.
The jail's not going to accept your W.
I'm not going to jail.
You are going to jail.
Yes, you are.
Okay, I got friends there so
who do I do on to the van?
If the cops weren't already convinced she was
either unstable or drunk, her behavior
seals the deal. Due to her condition, the
officers continued to display patience, but
it was becoming exceedingly difficult.
When the woman finally stops barking orders
at the officers like they're her personal
bellboys, they lay out two simple options.
Let us forgive these motherfuckers
trespassing assholes who trespass against
us.
They don't have to be Black. They can be
white, pink and purple. They still fucking
suck cock. Start over. Father, who art in
heaven. Thank you, my brother.
Hallowed by thy name. Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done. You'll be done,
motherfucker, as it is in heaven.
Undo the fucking cuffs.
Father, who art in heaven, hallowed by thy
name.
Thy kingdom come,
they will be done. Give us this day our daily
bread.
Forgive us our trespasses as we forgive these
fucking idiot trespassed against
us.
I'm gonna call my number on this.
Start over. Father-
She calling, she called me.
... who art in heaven.
Can't touch this. It's like five or six.
Hallowed by thy name. Thy kingdom come, they
will be done on earth. Father.
Blacks, whites, Jews.
Hallowed by thy name.
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done on Earth,
this fucking
Earth, Mother Earth, as it is in heaven. This
is what I tell you here.
All right, ma'am.
I'm not talking to him. You're the boss man.
Ma'am.
He's a peon. Shut up.
I'm gonna explain something to you, and if
you don't like it you don't have to like it,
but you need to hear it. Okay. Hold on. Let
me, let me
pray for your fucking ass real quick.
Okay. What I'm about to tell you-
Shut up
... is the difference between whether your
dog goes to animal control or whether you get
to animal control or whether you get to keep
your dog, okay?
Okay.
So I suggest you pay attention.
Hold on. I got to concentrate. Remember, I'm
100% veteran.
United States
Air Force, motherfucker.
Ma'am.
Ah.
You're smacked down with three mil-
Hold on. Ah.
Three military bases.
I gotta, I gotta-
You can't throw a rock without hitting-
... focus.
I've been trained by the United States
Government. You haven't.
Don't touch my fucking
jacket,
you pervert. You just fucked up my bag.
That's another one.
You can't even fish 'cause you have shitty
shoes. You definitely have an AR-15.
You kinda got one, but you don't know how to
use it. You got a plate holding your dick up.
Uh, badge, gun. And why is your gun
unhostered?
Why is his gun unhostered, motherfucker?
Bobby, Fabby, police, his gun is unhostered.
Okay, you gonna listen to what he has to say?
No, I wanna know why his gun's unhostered.
What makes you think it's unhostered?
Because I... I can tell you, fucking moron,
marksman sp-
gun specialist.
Well, that's good.
Now, fucking put that thing back on before
you talk to me.
All right. So-
I'm talking to you.
... I'm gonna give you one more chance and
then I'm gonna call animal control and send
your dog to animal control.
All right. Well-
I've called the jail and they won't take the
dog.
I knew they wouldn't. It's Christmas.
They won't, but what they will do is ROR you
for some misdemeanors.
What does that mean?
That means that you're not gonna be held on
bail.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They're going to process you and let you out
the front door.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Now, if you cooperate with me and cooperate
with them-
I don't know what a WOR is.
... I'll hold your dog till you come out the
front door.
You can have your dog back and we'll all go
on about our day.
I don't know what the fuck a WOR means.
And if you don't want to cooperate, release
on own recognizance.
It means they're gonna release you without
you having to go see a judge.
But I still haven't heard my rights yet.
Okay.
I'm under arrest.
Well, that's irrelevant.
No, it's not.
But do you want the dog to go to animal
control or would you like-
Well, you know the answer. We both know the
answers. Do I really have to answer you?
No. No, I do not want the dog.
Okay, so what we can do is if you cooperate,
once you get to the jail, they're going to
let you out on your own recognizance, which
means-
Good, let's go
... you don't have to see a judge, but-
We can take-
... you have to cooperate.
Can you undo these cuffs?
Cannot do that till we get to the jail.
Can you loosen them? Can you get me some
water?
Not right now.
Can you re- read me my rights? Can you put my
fucking handcuffs-... shoes on.
We'll let you put your shoes on.
How can I with my hands behind my back?
I see sandals right here.
Well, put 'em on, buddy. Here.
Oh, I can't do that.
If you choose not to put them on, that is
your choice.
I got, I got two little sweet... I prefer my
little black ones in there, buddy. They're
easier. I would prefer that I not had to come
here at all, ma'am.
Well, Merry-
To help you put your shoes on, but I will let
you put those sandals on.
Well, pull the black ones out. I don't want
those. I want those.
It's cold in jail, not those. There's
another-
Ma'am, when you get inside the jail, you
won't be wearing any shoes anyway.
You'll be wearing their sandals.
No, I won't.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll be wearing my shoes, not those 'cause
they have polices.
So, I'll take these ones. Can you wipe my-
Will you zip it?
... for me?
No, ma'am. No, I can't.
Who the's son are you? You're no friend of
mine. Yes, you are.
You can't even look at-
Ma'am, please stop.
No, I like you. What is your name?
Corporal D. Harris.
Harris D.
Where's your father from? New Mexico?
No.
You can't be related to me. There's no way
you're related to me.
Ma'am, how much you've had to drink today?
Not enough. I need to drink a lot more to
with you.
So-
All right
... where's my ID?
It's on fr- in front of my vest.
Why is it on your vest?
Because I took your ID to run you.
Honey, I'll never do you.
You got a on the top of your head. That's a
bad spot.
So-
You have $9 in cash.
That's all I got?
That's all that was there.
Okay, put the key and that in there.
Ma'am, I'm not putting the hotel key, room in
here. You don't stay at this hotel anymore.
I need proof when I sue you, so I want my
key.
This is a nice little video-
Hey-
... when you get an attorney.
Hold on. Hey.
Uh-uh.
I con.
What does your dog mean?
While this woman definitely deserves a longer
stay behind bars for the way
she treats her dog and the foul-mouthed
tirade she unleashes on the officers, she
was likely only looking at a day in jail.
That didn't stop her from packing like she
was heading off to serve a life
sentence.
Grab that sweatshirt.
Ma'am.
It's cold in jail. It's Sunday.
Ma'am, we are leaving now.
They're gonna take the sweatshirt from you as
soon as you get in there.
No, they won't. They'll just take the s-
sleeves out.
Can I get the dog?
Yeah.
Okay.
You can't touch my dog,
so just hand her my leash.
Come on, man.
Hold on. No, you can't touch my dog.
Come on. Come on, man.
Come on, Billy. Leave my dog alone. It's
against the law.
Federal law.
Where's my... There's my boo. Federal law.
Come on, Billy.
Give me your leash. You're not allowed to
touch her.
Alrighty. I'll your dad up, too. I'ma beat
his...
Do you know who he is? I ain't seen him a
long time, but you look just
like him.
Uh,
he knows I'ma... him up. Billy gotta go
potty.
[laughs]
Oh, my God.
You're killing me, bud. You're... airport
police.
You can't erase me. I'm not under arrest, am
I?
You are under arrest.
Okay. Put her back here with me.
She's gonna go to the bathroom first.
I gotta pee, too.
That's unfortunate. Please hold it. Have a
seat, ma'am.
Okay, let go.
Ma'am, have a seat in the car.
I have to get in my own way 'cause-
That's fine. Have a seat in the car.
I will. Give me a second 'cause he's a really
tight brother.
Harris,
let me get situated.
You, you don't even know how to fish, you...
You're gay too?
Hey, I thought-
Ma'am, scoot over here. I need to put your
seatbelt on you.
Which way?
Towards me.
Want me to suck your...
No.
I'm not gonna do that.
Scoot over towards me so I can put your
seatbelt on.
You, oh, you're rough. You like it rough? Oh.
Ma'am, let go of the seatbelt.
Oh.
You like it rough.
Ma'am, I hope that when you sober up, you
feel some measure of regret for the way that
you're acting. Why are you taking it off
after all this if you think I'm drunk?
All right, Ms. Lombardo.
To change the things I can.
I'm gonna let your dog ride in the back here
with you, all right? Do you understand?
Sure. Can she get in or you have to help her?
Can she get in?
Of course she... She can.
She can't, so you better help her. Come on,
boo. Uppity up. Uppity up.
Can you just give her a boost, moron?
Boosty moron. Boosty Boo Boo.
All right, ma'am.
Now-
We're going to the jail.
Go-
Once we get there, I have some forms for you.
All right, listen.
One of those forms-
Officer
... one of those forms is a ban form for this
facility.
Officer, I'm speaking.
Yes, ma'am. Yeah, I was talking to her.
Officer, I don't care. I'm speaking.
All right, ma'am.
I'm your senior.
Uh, you're gonna come back here when you
wanna get your stuff.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la,
la. If you don't have an officer with you,
you will be going right back to jail. La, la,
la, la, la, la, la. I'll talk to you. Very
mature.
I'll talk to you.
[laughs]
Can you hear me, you punk?
The officers were kind enough to let the dog
stay with her, a decision the dog would
probably file a formal complaint about if he
had a voice. Still, she eventually cooperated
and went off to jail. You'd think a night
behind bars might humble her a bit, but
prepare to be shocked.
I gotta say, man, this has been one of the
most entertaining rides I've ever had as an
airport cop. So, first off, you're his boss,
is that correct?
Yep.
Okay. Don't touch me.
Step outta the vehicle please, ma'am.
Don't tell me what to do. I'm speaking to
your boss.
Step outta the vehicle please, ma'am.
I want your supervisor here right now. Call
your boss.
Call the mayor, get him here. Don't touch my
dog. Come on.
Nope, dog's staying.
That's my dog.
Dog's staying.
No, you're not.
Dog is staying.
Shoot me. Shoot me.
You're going to jail, mother-
Stand right here.
You're going to jail, both of you. I'ma have
your...
Do you hear me? You are not my family.
I know who your family is, and it's snakes.
You've... Both know you are.
You touch me again, mother- Touch me again.
Stand against the wall.
I already got assault on...
... ch the wall, please. Hey, how are you?
I'm all right. I'm patting you down. What's
the charge?
Criminal trespass and obstruction.
Is this-
Yeah.
How do you touch my pooch here?
Dog's in the car.
Okay, you can turn around for me.
No, I don't want you to touch at all.
All right, you can turn around. Come on off
right here.
He doesn't-
... away from me. [car door thuds] That
mother [cutting out] snake.
Yeah, don't open the car.
Okay, got you. -Turn around, ma'am. Shut up.
-Turn around, ma'am. I'm talking to her.
You're going to jail motherf... They're gonna
you up your... You're gonna love it.
[clicks tongue]
All right, so we're here to go-
Okay, these two mothers are bad boys. Do you
know what that is?
Picked this up?
You murderers. Hey, honey. How are you?
Hi.
Good, how are you?
My stuff in.
Good morning boys.
Good morning. How are you?
You know how I am, motherf...
How are you? Because I'm going to beat you.
Man.
Oh, man.
Fuck.
Well, that's not very nice. [car door thuds]
Yeah, turn around and face the car.
Are you the boss?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, so we got some problems that I wanna
talk about today.
Left leg. Lift it up.
Raise her leg up, so she can get the
handcuffs.
Miss Lombardo, here's what's going to happen.
Lombardo, excuse me.
You know what?
The things from your room are by your car
over there.
Where? Are they outside in the street?
Yeah, your dog is in the back seat of my car.
You're gonna sign for your dog, you're gonna
take your things, you're gonna get in your
car and you're gonna leave the property.
First don't know-
If you
of all, I
return to this property, you'll be going back
to jail.
I don't hear you right now because you lost
something down here.
Ma'am.
Hold on, hold on.
Something down there.
Yourself there, make sure her car did not
move.
Yep. Lift your leg.
Ma'am.
Lift your shoe.
You're the boss.
You're gonna sign for your dog.
Okay.
You're gonna take your dog back. You're gonna
put your things in your car and you're gonna
leave the property.
Did you feed my dog?
If you come back to this property, you are
going to go to jail.
Did you feed the dog?
Do you understand?
Man, not a problem. Did you feed the dog?
No, I didn't.
What time is it?
I don't know.
If you wanted the care to happen to your dog,
you shouldn't have gone into jail.
Get me my dog.
Come with me. Come on.
Did you clean that pen off?
Ma'am, if you don't sign it, you don't get
the dog.
Give me that.
I'll call Animal Control right now.
Oh, where am I signing?
Right there.
Am I hurting your feelings in front of your
boss and your friends?
Thank you, ma'am.
Did they all know you're gay now? Hey,
babies.
She can get out by herself.
Come on, pup.
Don't touch my dog. Hey.
Ma'am.
Hey!
Ma'am. [car door thuds] Ma'am, you're
blocking traffic. Step over there, please.
That's not my car you're blocking, dumb...
Take your things, get in your car and leave
the property, please. [door opens] .
Oh, God.
Miss Lombardo.
Yes?
I'm gonna give you 10 minutes and then I'm
gonna take you to jail for trespassing.
Take your time, buddy. You're all set.
[driverS laughing]
She was charged with criminal trespass and
obstruction.
[keyboard clacking] No matter how unhinged
she was, at least she acted her age.
Our next suspect is no better than a teething
toddler.
[crying]
Please, I want get out, please.
As if getting caught shoplifting isn't
embarrassing enough, this woman manages to
make it even worse by throwing a full-blown
tantrum.
[Crying]
I didn't even get to eat my dinner.
On April 13th, 2024, Florida officers
responded to a call from a
local Walmart about a woman accused of
shoplifting markers.
She insisted she had money in her car, but
don't they all once they're caught
red-handed? One look at the CCTV footage
though and her story fell apart faster than
her story fell apart faster than her alibi.
I knocked her for trespassing warning,
but I didn't talk to her and ask her any
questions in reference to the theft.
So, I'm gonna read her and start asking
questions.
She already trespassed?
Yep. I didn't ask her anything in reference
to that.
No,
sir.
Hey, ma'am, I told you there's two gentlemen
that are gonna come and talk to you
here in a few.
What's, what's your name again?
Jessica.
Jessica?
Yeah.
All right, meet me and Miranda.
Um, remember our game plan. So,
Kyle asked, Kyle, did you grab her driver's
license?
She had a picture of it on her phone.
Okay, all right. Your driver's license is
suspended, right? I mean, we're not worried
about that here. Do you have anybody working
here?
My friend, she's outside.
Okay.
All right.
She has my card and my wallet.
Okay. Remember our game plan.
Okay.
The first thing I would do, I would talk to
Lashonda.
See what Lashonda has. She can chill right
here.
Hold on.
What do you got in your pouch?
Just
stuff for at home.
Do you mind if we do a pat down on you?
Yeah, that's fine.
Say that again, I can't hear you.
You can do that.
Okay, stand up for me, please.
What I would do is ask her to take everything
out of her pouch.
This is mine, because I got it from
Walgreens. Those are mine.
Okay.
These are mine.
Those ones are all theirs.
Can you put the paper down on the ground?
So, what I would do is just place her, but we
don't necessarily have to do a pat down
because her, everything's inside.
Um, ma'am, do you mind? This is what I would
do.
Just lift your shirt up and spin around.
Are you good with that?
I'm good with it too. You, you can
put your things back in here and just set
that on the floor. We'll go ahead and
interview you with Lashonda. I viewed her on
CCTV,
um, opened up her hand package
pins,
um, that she selected over here in
stationary.
Mm-hmm.
So fast-forward a little bit.
Well, she was placing it in her-
Into her little fanny pack.
Oh, okay.
So, she must have stopped her hand here.
Did she actually try to walk out with it?
She did. Um, I stopped her right outside, on
the sidewalk.
Right outside, okay.
Show you that clip next.
Lashonda, what, what's the total value amount
of the items?
Um, 32.84.
Hey, I was just going outside to get my card,
please.
And then, boom.
So, what you doing, Sean? I, I, I know, I
know the answer of what you wanna do.
Uh, prosecute trespass. We already did the
trespass, so yeah, prosecute.
Fair enough.
At this point, you're trespassed. It's just
that this guy doesn't want to talk to you
until he figured out what's gonna be next.
So, these were a pen, permanent marker?
Um, pens, permanent marker-
And where are you guys going to put them?
... and more
markers. I think they, I think they're all
markers. I think one type is a pen and the
other ones are markers. Okay. Gonna ask you
some questions, but before I do,
gonna read you your Miranda, okay?
All right.
I'm under arrest. [cries]
We're doing an investigation to figure that
out, all right?
Okay.
Do you understand each of these rights I have
explained to you?
Yeah.
Having these rights in mind, do you wish-
[crying]
...
to talk with me now?
I guess. I don't know.
But do you understand each of these rights
that I explained to you?
For
the most part. [crying]
Would you like for me to read them again so
you can fully understand?
No, I'm still not gonna fully understand. I
don't comprehend it.
[cries]
Okay.
Do you still wish to talk to me?
All right, so e- explain to me, uh, what-
what was
the whole process of- of you
inside the Walmart?
[cries] Some of those were al- those were
already opened. [cries]
They were already opened in the aisle?
They were already opened in the aisle.
[cries] All I did was take one or two.
I was gonna try them. I wanted to c- I was
going outside to get my card.
All right.
I swear.
Even if they were open,
you know you can't just put them in your
pouch and leave, correct?
All right. And then on the, on the cameras,
we see you opening
the packaging for the- for the markers.
[coughs] No, those were already open.
We have video.
I promise. I promise.
Okay.
I swear. You can zoom in. They... Those two
were already open.
All I did was take one... take the marker
out.
All right, so all the... all the-
The other one doesn't-
All those item... All those items there, when
you look, you didn't intend to- to pay for
it, you just walked out.
No, I was going to get my card.
All right, so you-
I asked the lady up front to hold them, but
there's things that I had.
So,
the person who was working, they held it for
you?
Yeah, it's up front.
Okay. So, instead of you leaving, why not
have your friend go get your card for you?
You said you have a friend, right?
Because my phone was dead. I just plugged it
in in here.
Oh, so your friend was waiting for you
outside?
All right.
No, she went in here shopping and I was going
outside to try to find her so
I could get the card.
[coughs]
Okay.
'Cause I had money sent to her Cash App.
[crying]
So you had money on your card, but it was
inside your vehicle?
It was in her bag, in her purse. That's all.
I was going outside to get it. You can ask
the service station.
All right.
I promise.
So- so you may have left some items with
them, but you s- you did have stuff in
your... in your-
Yes, I did. [cries]
You know you're not allowed to do that,
right?
And I didn't buy it.
You know you're not allowed to do that,
right?
I don't know.
No matter- no matter the amount?
I don't know. [music]
Sure, the shoplifting total was only $32.84,
but it was never about the money.
Given the chance, she probably would have
kept going.
The cops knew that, and the moment she
realized she wasn't getting off easy, she
ditched the excuses and dove straight into a
tantrum bad enough to embarrass a child.
Do you- do you take any- any medications or
anything like that?
Not yet. Monday, I have an appointment with
mental health.
[cries]
Where?
In Port St. Lucie with...
with Bright... uh,
with Bright Life.
With- with who?
With Bright Life.
Fright Life?
No, Bright-
Bright Life?
Life.
When is- when is that appointment?
Monday.
On Monday?
Okay.
Monday at 1:00.
All right. Um...
Sorry, it's at 12:00 'cause she has an
opening between 11:00
and 1:00. [cries]
All right, so- so based on my
investigation here, um, can you stand up? Do
you mind standing up?
No. Please, why? Please don't take me.
I promise I gave them to her.
You left-
I wasn't leaving.
... you left the store yourself.
I didn't even make it out the door yet.
Jessica, stand up.
[crying] I
can't. I won't get out. Please.
Jessica, stand up.
[crying] Please, I won't get out.
Please.
Turn around. Turn around and face the wall.
[crying] Please, I won't get
out. [cries] I'm
sorry.
Just go
up to the office and fill out a form.
Please, I don't have anyone's phone number.
Okay.
Please, sir, please. Please. [cries] What if
I'm at Meijer and was being honest?
Let's adjust this.
Is that the right thing to do?
Look, the- the- the way they were, she
definitely slipped them.
Oh,
please. [cries]
Hold on. One second.
Please.
Keep going. Keep going.
I was gonna pay for them.
Okay. That's good.
Please, sir, please. Please. Ma'am,
please. I'm homeless.
Keep going. Keep going.
Please, I can just pay for them. Please, I
wanted to
help. Please, I won't get my health...
Please, I won't get my health...
Come see me.
Please, I won't get my health... Please.
[cries]
Jessica, stop.
Is this charger yours?
No.
It's just your phone?
Yes.
Can you please give that- my bag to my
friend, please?
Please?
I don't know about that.
Oh, please, can you give her my bag? Oh,
please.
This is all my markers. Please. [cries]
Please, ma'am.
Jessica, come to line one, please.
Can I please blow my nose, please?
Please, I'm sorry. Please, people do this all
the time and you let them
go.I can't even
think. [crying]
Well, here's the thing, you can't-
Why?
... because you don't have ties to Indian
River County.
I do.
If you had ties to Indian River County-
My kid is here, my sister's here.
If you had ties to Indian River County, you
had an address here.
I do.
You can just write me what it is. It's still
a criminal charge, it's still the same thing.
It is what it is. I know, but-
It is what it is
... please don't take me there. Please, I'll
pay.
[crying]
That decision's already been made, which is a
properly made decision by Deputy Saunders.
Please, I was gonna pay. I even told her I
would pay.
Well, well, Walmart don't... they don't play.
I know. I'm sorry, I didn't mean to. I'm not
in the right state of mind.
Walmart doesn't play around, they prosecute.
That's... and that... when they wanna press
charges,
we have to serve them the way they want.
Please don't put me in jail.
Please, I-
It's a $500 bond. You have to-
[crying] I don't have $500.
- shert down.
I don't even have but 40 bucks. Please.
I
promise I'll pay the 40 and leave the
markers.
I don't believe you. Can you mail them in?
I have my kid here, my son is here.
We'll search. Please call him now. Now.
I have-
Let him come down for a few moments.
I'm raised here, born and raised. I've, I've
lived here my whole life.
Timothy's on harassment, Joanna's on reckless
negativity.
[crying]
Like, us one, something like that.
Mm-hmm.
Like, way down the road as insanity, so.
Please. Please.
[clears throat]
I have my kid here. I will come to court.
I've did my time here already.
Apparently she doesn't have bail money. Well,
how would she if she's spent it on weed?
Clearly this woman needs to set her
priorities straight, and jail is the perfect
place to do that.
Please, I don't have $500 to sit there
forever all day by myself.
You got, uh, these two copies here? Do we
need two or just one?
Um, just by myself.
Do, do you want him, do you want him to give
your friend a call to tell, to tell her what
happened so she's not waiting for you?
Yeah.
She can't remember?
Please, no one's in my phone.
Can we look forward in your phone?
Yeah.
We're not searching your phone.
No, please. Can you please go to my car log?
Hi, Tyler. What's your name?
Service.
Holly.
I'm not gonna be able to get out. [crying]
Please, I have
an appointment on Monday with Bright Lights.
They can vouch for me and
hold my ties. I promise. [crying] I can
call her.
She can vouch for me.
My son's here, my sister's here.
I was born and raised here. I lived in Vero
Beach.
We'll call her in a little while once we
clear the scene and let her know what's
happened. All right. So you got, you got
this?
Mm-hmm.
I'll grab this. You, you just maintain
control of your suspect.
Stand up.
Well, can I please wipe my face off?
Sure you can.
Can you just wipe it for me? [crying]
I'll, I'll turn around. Yes, that's all
right.
Okay.
No, please. I'm
sorry. I'm so
sorry.
My kid's here. Please, I promise, I have all
my ties to the world
here.
Please, it's really cold out. They're gonna
make me freeze in there.
That's,
that's starting to get real.
Please, I, I don't feel good. I don't wanna
do this.
Please, I'll never get out [crying] in time
for my
mental health appointment. Please, sir,
I don't understand.
I don't understand. Step up.
[crying] I don't understand. Oh, can you give
her my bag, please?
Her car's right over there.
This car?
Look, her trunk is open. Look! Please.
Whose car is it?
Please. It's that Jeep right over there, in
front of that handicap spot right there.
The what? That's-
Just give her my, my fanny pack and keep my
phone.
Okay.
Please. [crying]
All right, what do we need to do?
You can go ask her, please, good morning.
Stay there while we wait to see Jay?
I have mental health on Monday. Please don't
let me miss it.
Please,
I'm so sorry.
I'll drive to jail. You just take care of the
radio, but we'll wait until Kyle.
[crying]
Please,
sir, please. I have n- I have no money.
I just have enough to cover the markers, $30.
Keep going.
$30 and I have to pay $500.
So?
It was six markers.
All right, ready, go.
Hold the mileage.
Oh, God, please. Look, there she goes. Look,
there she goes.
Please, can you give her my fanny pack,
please?
He, he gave it to her.
We did.
Huh?
He gave it to her.
Okay. Can she, can she just pay for me?
Dispatch has been updated.
Please.
You let her know I got her bag?
Okay, um, okay. Thank you.
Oh, no, please. Holly, please. [crying]
I don't understand. You guys have let other
people go before
for more than this. I have ties, I swear to
God. Why me?
You know, the price went down the minute she
changed those markers, elf?
She changed the box. She counted it for 31
with that big case.
That's not fair. I was gonna pay her, uh, for
them,
and she could've kept them. [crying]
I'll never make my appointment.
I didn't even get to eat my dinner.
I'm gonna freeze. Oh, could you get my jacket
from her?
Oh, it's not fair.
[crying]
45 minutes, right? Yeah.
My son goes to Glenville Baptist and my
sister works there.
Please.
Why did I get the treaty?
Oh!
Oh, god, [crying] please.
[police sirens] Jessica, do you have anything
on you?
What do you mean?
Do you have anything illegal in your bra or
anywhere else?
[police sirens]
Yes. I have a little bit of weed on me.
Literally the size of a penny. [laughs]
Please don't...
Okay. Dude, that's good because
if you brought that into jail,
it would be an ex-
Call me possession of contraband. [police
sirens]
Yes. All right, good. N- now we're getting
somewhere.
If it's under 20 grams, we're not gonna
charge you with it.
It's literally the size of my thumb.
Where is it?
It's in my bra.
Okay.
I forgot about it.
That's okay.
W- where... i- if it's under 20 grams, we
will not charge you.
Okay. [police sirens]
Thank you for being honest.
There's no reason to c- for you to catch a
felony.
I've been 20 years on this call, cop.
There's no reason for you to catch a felony
for this.
[police sirens] Ah, I'm gonna be in here all
weekend.
I have that mental health appointment on
Monday, please.
The woman was charged with petty theft.
Detective Dale always says it's almost
impossible to reason with entitled suspects
with entitled suspects with main character
syndrome. Most of the time, cops can spot it
from a mile away, but they still give them a
chance to clear their story. And nine times
out of 10, it ends the same way, with
handcuffs. This isn't the first time we've
caught Karens in full action either. So, if
you're enjoying the ride so far, make sure to
leave a like, and hit that subscribe button
for more.
The lights in the background can go off.
Otherwise, I'll sue you, you and you.
On March 1st, 2024, a Lake County officer was
patrolling when he noticed a
white Chevy swerving like it was auditioning
for a demolition derby.
At first, he wasn't planning to pull it over,
until the car nearly hit the curb and came to
a shaky stop. The driver's choice of parking
was a big giveaway that everything was not
well inside the vehicle.
10-4.
Montana
450 to Montana 392. Can you be 51?
26.
Where, where you coming from?
I am coming from, um...
Do
you
have your, your registration?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Um, why do I feel like you're speeding?
D- do you know why I pulled you over?
Um, was it... I was speeding? I don't know.
Maybe.
So, w- w- when I'm coming down the road, you,
you swerved and avoided-
I came from, I came from
back ass, and I avoided something.
Yeah, you, you swerved-
And I remember going very-
Hold on. Listen, listen, l- listen-
... far away from what I was avoiding-
Listen to me.
And then I turned left.
Yeah. So you came down this road and you
was all on this side of the road driving.
I had to stop my vehicle for you to get back
over.
I turned around to follow you and you were
just about crashing to the, over the curb
over the curb over there. Until I got behind
you.
I'm sorry, what curb?
The curb on Alexander. And then, as I-
I'm sorry, what was I gonna crash into?
Listen, and then... And then, as I, as I
pulled you over, do you know you came over
the curb into someone's yard?
My goodness. Your light is reflecting in my
pupil.
So, look, do,
do you see where you're at? You're, you're...
You crossed the curb and-
Uh, you, you have now pulled me over, and
what else am I
supposed to do but pull over into the most-
No, all you had to do was pull over to the
side over here.
My mother, my mother told me to pull over in
the most,
uh, credible place.
Okay.
As in, if I were to pull over with somebody
rather their
yard, and then this place-
No, you, you crossed the, you crossed the
whole curb
to... I forget, I-
To get into a place...
This is a one-way road, sir.
Okay, okay. Just get back in the car. Okay,
get back in the, get back in the car for me.
Just step back in the car for me.
No.
Step back in the car for me.
Okay.
This is a one-way road.
Okay, step back in the car. I, I...
Step... Get back in the car.
Hunter.
Get back in the car.
Hunter?
Either you get back in the car or I detain
you.
Right here in the car.
Yes, sir. Um, who are you?
Just take a note. Just take a seat.
Who are you? Oh, wow.
Why are there so many people?
Here, can you still record? Can you still
record and let me show you what happened?
Oh my God, I am not like a robber or
something.
No, we're not. Did we say that?
Can I go back home?
No, we cannot.
Like, guys-
Sorry. Sorry
Why can I not go back home?
I'll be right back.
Okay, he's gonna talk to you in just a
second. Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
Nope, don't send...
He's grabbing your purse.
My purse,
my wallet.
Okay, that's perfectly fine.
Going into the purse.
She's, she's gone. Oh, she's gone. Yeah. But
it's not the same one. Oh, it's not? Okay.
You didn't see her tattoos? Okay.
Here. She's,
she's, she's live. Yeah, can you... I need to
talk to Mason.
Can you tell, watch out for me?
Check my car without my permission. We have
to talk to him.
He wants to talk. He wants to talk.
Without my permission, so- Can you wait right
here for him, okay? Without my permission.
So... Um, are you guys looking for somebody
specific?
No. No.
Then why are you guys doing this to me?
Well, usually we don't, like, stop people at
this, late at night, so...
And, and my person-
So why did you guys do this when I didn't do
anything wrong?
Because I haven't done anything wrong and I
have kids and a husband.
[crying]
Okay.
So tell me,
why did you stop me, sir?
I don't know. I, I wasn't the one that
stopped you, so I can't say.
You don't know?
Where the [beep] is my phone?
So I'm driving on 11, and she's on the
opposite side of the road.
Coming at you?
Coming at me. So I was just like, "Stop." I'm
like, "Oh, what is she doing?" She swerved
back over and the car get to shaking. I'm
like-
Are you out of your mind? Did you really-
"Not right." So I just made a U-turn, you
know-
Because I had it done!
I'm not gonna do a traffic stop yet. I, I
turn around and she's like at the stop sign,
like at the stop sign, like facing this way.
At 11th?
On Alexander.
On Alexander?
On, on a stop sign, I'm like, "Oh yeah, I'm,
I, I...
it's just..."
So then how'd you guys end up here?
So I flipped my lights on back there.
Yeah.
And I'm calling at the, uh,
the 28th. She stops and then goes again, and
then comes around here.
Come over here, makes a U-turn
and then hopped the curb. [laughs]
She's definitely... I think she's under the
influence. I smell the alcohol.
I smell she-
She's pissed herself.
And she cannot give me... She-
But I just want to make sure-
She's not making any stops.
She's not?
Yeah. So...
What the [beep] do you want?
[laughs]
What do you want?
I wanna know why-
Look at me more.
I wanna know how you ended up on the, the,
the grass here?
Because I pulled over and there is no way to
pull over on
a one-way street, other than turning into a
U-turn to pull over so that other civilians
can
still pull forward and make their way through
their route without me being
in their way. Is there any other questions?
I don't have any more.
[camera clicking] This is when the officers
hit her with a crucial bit of reality she's
far too hammered to grasp. She's drunk and
it's time for a sobriety test.
You'd think her instant agreement means
she'll comply, but you're in for a surprise.
Okay, I have reason to believe that you're
under the influence of alcohol or some
substance.
Okay.
So
the next step is doing the sobriety field
exercises.
Okay.
Do you consent to doing
the exercises?
Field?
Consent. Do you... It's a yes or no. If you
don't wanna do 'em, you say no.
If you are willing to do them-
Yeah, I'll do your, I'll do your field.
All right.
Please.
She got some tape and everything.
Can you come this way with me?
I have been
pulled over.
Please.
You want to come up on the-
Thank you. Let me see.
Rachel.
Rachel, can you come this way with me?
Yes, sir.
Can you put all your bags and stuff inside
of,
inside of your, your car?
All of my bags?
Yes.
But like at illegal police base?
No, I just want, just want you to put your
bags-
Did I kill somebody? [crying]
No.
Did I hurt somebody?
No, but-
Someone tell me the reason why all of this is
necessary.
I told you, when I was driving down, down the
street, you swerve.
You was on the other side of the street.
Yeah, I swerved. I just got back from my
girlfriend, my very best friend
Erica's house. And she's on [crying] the
street that the
shell station is on. And I was trying to get
my [beep] music
right and I might've swerved
trying to get my music 'cause she's on the
shell station street, but I promise you
I'm not [beep]
anything up. I'm not gonna kill somebody.
Come on.
I'm not gonna hurt anybody.
Come this way. Just... No, no, no, no. You,
you, you good right here. They're putting
tape down. Just walk this way with me. You,
you can walk regular. Walk with me.
No.
I'm not moving unless somebody tells me to
move.
You can move. Come on.
How and where?
Just walk up to me.
In the regular walking
r-
Go right around.
I'm not risking it. It's my best friend's
house and then my
children are at the other house. It's like
less than a mile.
Okay, just... Okay, just walk this way with
us. Walk this way.
I'm not okay with it. You guys are [beep] .
It's a [beep] job. Tell me what I'm doing,
sir.
Walk towards me.
[cries]
There we go. All right, that's fine. You can
stop. You can stop.
Let's take that here.
[crying] You guys are [beep]
jobs. You guys are so [beep] .
Hey, let me borrow your little, your little
My what?
D-U... Yeah.
Yeah.
Can I [beep] go home, bro? I have kids and my
husband.
All right. Don't cry.
Like, no. I gotta go through this check
[crying] and this check-
And we have to make sure-
... and this check.
... make sure everything is okay.
Bro, I get home. I wanna go home.
Well, if everything goes well on this and we
see that you're okay to drive-
Obviously, dude, I've had the most-
Then that's-
... the most chill-
Yep, we're good. We're good.
... like everything.
She's gonna start here in just a second,
okay?
Yeah, just a second.
I had the most chill ever- No, what do you
mean, dude?
They wouldn't have pulled me over for no
reason.
I mean, if everything goes well here then no.
You're lying, you're a liar.
If everything goes well, you're good. You're
all good.
But you're a liar though.
If you can show me that you are okay to
drive.
Because I've been in this situation where I
didn't have anything in the car and people
have been like, "Oh, we're gonna take you to
jail anyways.
And then you have to do this, that, and the
other." [crying] And then people have [beep]
taken
like completely innocent human beings away
and taking them and so like, I'm scared.
Okay, so I, I'm-
We're not taking them.
Everybody's getting... I literally
just did that.
No, I asked you to move up to me. I told you,
I specifically said this is not a part of
anything. Yeah, guys, okay. Whatever.
Here, put your clothes back on. Come here.
Let's work somewhere.
Okay, look. Right here.
Whatever, guys. Okay. All right, guys.
Look, face me.
Get the [beep] out my face. You lie about me
doing your sobriety test.
You have-
Because I did your sobriety test.
So if you can stop your attitude right now
and do that.
I did it. Can you acknowledge her?
Or we'll
No, if you, if you, if you don't a-
Acknowledge her is sideways.
L- listen, you can listen to her. You can
listen to her.
I'm gonna go ahead and do whatever the [beep]
they tell me to do.
[camera clicking] This is a grown woman who
somehow made it through life without learning
how a field sobriety test works. Talk about
being completely out of touch.
But nothing snaps you back to reality quite
like the cold click of handcuffs.
Place your feet
together and your arms by your side....
keep your head straight and follow the
stimulus with your eyes and your eyes only.
Do not move your head. Do you understand?
I do, sir.
Nice.
Oh, wow. We're adding extra efficiency.
D- you said you understand the instructions,
but-
Turn that light off-
No-
... because my instructions don't include an
extra
LEO light on me. Do they?
I'm gonna read this again. It says, "Follow
with your eyes and your eyes only, and do not
move your head. With your hands by your
side-"
Right, and, and that bitch-
"... and feet together."
... goes off.
No.
Right?
No?
All right. Pull a judge out here. Tell me
what they think.
Well, you're not following instructions,
first of all.
My instructions involve a blue light-
... were to put your feet together, put your-
... in my face and not my [beep]
Can put that light behind his back.
Put your feet together and hands by your
side.
They've been here this whole time.
Okay. And...
Uh-huh.
Follow with your eyes and your eyes only.
Do not move your head. It's not... Don't look
at me.
So until the light that's in my eyes-
The light is not coming off
... from the background-
The light is not coming off.
The light from the background can go off,
otherwise I'll sue
you, you and you
for the same thing.
Okay.
Turn it off.
So we're gonna just go to the next exercise.
No, we're gonna go ahead and go with the same
exercise-
No, 'cause I, I, I explained multiple times
you have not been listening
... and you are gonna turn that-
Listen to me-
... light off?
Li- li- listen to me.
Thank you.
I'm, I'm the one conducting the exercises.
I'm giving the instructions.
Does the exercise say, "Side, side please
hold the light"?
Are you gonna, are you gonna listen to me,
what I say?
"Side please hold the light."
Okay, look.
So s- s-
... or you're lying in my face one more
[beep] time, I'll sue you with the rest of
them. Okay, I'm ready.
Right for you, sir.
Let's go. Let's go.
What do I need to-
Oh, we're gonna come up here to this line
right here.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, oh. Okay.
All right. Yep.
You're gonna put your... You're gonna... A
lei.
Mm-hmm. What else am I doing, honey?
You're gonna place your left foot on the
line-
Mm-hmm
...
and your right foot directly in front of it.
Left-
And my right foot directly in front of it
until the end of the line, right?
Get the [beep] out my way.
You listen to the instructions-
Free my speech. Get the [beep] out my way.
Either listen to the instructions,
or we just don't do it.
Okay, let's listen to the instructions.
okay.
Get the [beep] out my way. And tell me the
instructions.
I'm telling you the instructions.
Get the fuck out my way.
Place your left foot on the line and your
right foot directly-
Oh, my God. Let me call my husband.
Can I help you two?
Yeah.
Sir, please put your hands behind your back
for me.
I-
You're under arrest at this point, yes.
No. No.
You resist, you're gonna have charges.
No, I'm not. I'm trying-
Yes, you are. No, you're not.
No, I'm not.
Okay. I got it here.
Relax.
I'm trying to call my husband.
Nope, you're under arrest at this point.
And I'm trying to walk.
I'm trying to walk.
No. Give me your phone. Give me your phone.
No, I'm trying to walk.
I'm trying to walk. I'm trying to walk
without my husband.
He's-
Cool. You're in cuffs.
I'm trying to walk without my husband. I'm
trying to walk. I hate you, bitch.
You have no [beep] idea.
Come on, girl.
Thank you, I do, too, love.
Give me my phone back. Right over there.
How?
How? How?
Grab her her handcuffs.
How?
You guys didn't give me any [beep] test.
Stop resisting.
Resisting?
Don't... Sorry.
I want my phone. Oh, my God, guys.
In the car. In the car.
Guys, I will do it if you speak to me.
No, you just plopped down when you did that.
Listen, you have no idea what you're doing.
The minor I have-
Get in. Get in the car. In the car.
What you're doing?
Party driver on.
Please don't do this.
Yep, you're going up.
Have her hands behind her back.
I'm, I'm going to get in and you guys are...
Are you guys-
No, you're not. You're sitting there as we're
pulling you in. Put it in.
I would like my phone in a-
She's got it.
You guys are kidding me.
Her behavior keeps getting worse at the
station, to the point where the cops have no
choice but to step in harder. A quick breath
test shows exactly why she'd been
acting up. Her breath sample was 2.7 times
over the legal limit.
But being drunk doesn't give you a free pass
to act like a loud, out of control
mess.
I didn't even get a chance to s- say [beep]
You have no right to
arrest me.
I was always available
to do the check-in and you guys had no [beep]
like
point where you didn't all the way with me.
You guys didn't even do it. You guys didn't
even do a check-in with me.
What, you thought you were gonna smash my
face in the bar?
No, I did not.
Is that what you thought you were gonna get?
No, you were resisting. That's why you not in
the seat of the car.
No, I didn't. I wasn't resisting. I said I
would take it.
I said, "Let me do it."
I said, "Let me do it." I said, "Let me give
the drunken
test." Let me do it.
Let me do it. Now we live.
That's for now. Hold on, let me see that. Oh,
yeah.
All of it and you didn't let me do it.
You did... You, you did not cooperate.
You didn't let me do it.
You still haven't-
Well, it's, it's-
... let us do it.
It's too late, now.
You won't let me... Oh, it's too late? You
can't let me be sober?
You're not allowed to let me be sober?
You can't let me out of the car and do a
sobriety test and then let me
go?
You can't do that?
You didn't have the time?
My door, 458-
What's the problem?
I'm 97LCJ65M.
What's the problem? Why couldn't you have
done the tests?
Uh-huh.
Because you're gonna get sued. You're gonna
get [beep] sober.
78734.
Yeah? You're gonna... You're not gonna do the
test?
Do you have a DNI?
You won't do the test?I
didn't do anything.
Can you talk?
I didn't do anything.
Can I talk?
Yes, I would love to talk.
I'd love to talk about everything.
No. Can I talk?
I know you talked.
Why is everybody holding me? What is going
on?
Because you're piling up three people right
now.
Why is this happening? I didn't do anything
wrong.
Rachel.
I wasn't even drunk enough-
Well, obviously having a little too much
... to be pulled over and-
It's false
... and to be-
Calming. Shh.
And to be like, be put aside-
Rachel, Rachel.
Whatever the word is.
Listen to me.
To be-
Listen to me
... to be arrested.
Listen to me.
I didn't do anything. [crying]
Get out of the way. Listen to me.
I didn't do anything.
Listen to me.
Good question.
My entire job here tonight-
So why is everybody taking-
... my entire job
... my earrings out?
Listening.
[cries] Why am I letting everybody take my
hair out and my earrings
out? What's going on? Why is this happening?
If you let me talk, I can share this with
you.
But then why have they told me?
I'm trying.
Why-
Keep talking.
Where's my other ear? [laughs]
You keep talking. I can't help.
What did I do wrong? I'm not psychotic to the
point where
you need to pull my earrings. You guys are
all nuts.
I did not do [beep] .
Why do you always think-
One ring.
All I did was being sick.
Sure.
Gonna try and talk her.
Thank you for securing me.
What did you want to just watch?
Rachel-
I am madly in love with her. I swear I would
never do anything to
hurt anybody on the police force, because I
respect the police force and
I appreciate what they do.
You're a waste of time.
That's not very nice.
Please help me. [cries]
Waste of time, trying to talk to them.
I'm good. Oh, yeah.
What's your name, Officer?
My name is Senior Officer Parker with the
Police Department.
Officer Parker, finally. Eh, look at me
that's looking me
in my goddamn eyes and talking to me and tell
me what's going on.
Why the [beep] am I in this [beep] thing-
Calm down.
... when I am so cooperative? And why people
are trying
to [beep] things off of me when I can pull my
own ring off
of me-
I'm sorry.
... and give it to them. What the fuck is-
[laughs] that's why.
Rachel, from what I understand, you were
brought here-
What's her name?
You were brought here-
I wanna know her name.
Okay, and-
Moore.
Officer Parker, what's your name?
I, I-
Officer Moore.
Moore?
Yes.
Rachel, Rachel, my job here is that, is to do
an
observation-
Officer Moore laughing at me while I'm trying
to explain-
Rachel-
... that I am completely cooperative.
And this bitch is laughing at me while I'm
cooperative and willing to work with
Officer Parker.
This bitch is fucking laughing at me. Could
someone remove her?
I tell you what, can we talk in the other
room?
And that bitch is laughing at me?
Oh my God! [laughs]
Rachel, can we talk in the other room?
I will remove myself. How loose are you?
Look at her.
How loose are you?
Rachel, can we talk in the other room?
Please? Like all of y'all, like I took, like
I had two
beers and then one shot in between the two
beers, and
like you guys are [beep] me up like I've done
like six tequila
shots in a-
Calm down.
... off the day trying to get [beep] up.
Like why am I not-
Calm down.
Why am I not allowed to go pee if I have to
go pee if you guys...
I'm sorry.
Relax.
Hey.
Okay, we're gonna wait one minute and then
we're gonna do another sample, okay?
No.
I'm okay.
Three times for the mother- [beep] that
wanted Rachel to go to jail.
Hey, hey, hey. Three, two, one. [fingers
snapping]
You ready to blow?
I want one.
Yeah.
Deep breath. Deep breath for me, Rachel.
Ready?
I wanna go home.
You have the right to an attorney and have
him or her present with you before and
during- I want Russell.
... any questioning. Do you understand each
of these rights I have explained to you?
I passed every test. I did-
Do you know-
... get zero questions.
Look at me. I passed every test.
Okay, can you listen?
Why am I sitting here-
Okay, listen. Listen. Do you-
Why? Look at me.
Do you understand your rights?
What's his name? W what?
That's it. Yeah, if you don't wanna talk,
then walk out.
So I'll ask you, do you understand your
rights that I've explained to you?
I passed all of the tests.
Do you wanna try again or you good?
He made me pee myself. [beep] over here.
Do you want-
I just tried to hold myself so
bad.
We're done. She was charged with DUI and
resisting an officer without violence and
refusal of DUI test after suspended license.
Unfortunately, she's not our worst suspect
today.
Our last one takes that cake.
Oh, fuck you. Go now.
Stay off me. What the hell?
Go [censored] now.
On February 13th, 2023, Florida officers were
called to a hospital where
a woman was refusing to leave. When they
showed up, they were greeted by a loudmouth
whose meltdown could put a nuclear plant to
shame.
You're an [beep] .
What's going on?
I love this. Oh my gosh! They just let them
see everything
that they shouldn't have seen.
So [beep] you.
Whoa.
[beep] you.
Hey, I just got here. Relax.
And him.
You're making a scene.
[beep] you.
What are you making a scene for?
I'm good.
She was too intoxicated.
Oh, is she?
Get the [beep] out.
Who- who's she with?
Go and see what they didn't see.
I didn't say anybody-
Go and see what they didn't see! Go and see
what they didn't see!
Hey, how are you getting home?
Because you're a [beep] .
How are you getting home?
Oh, [beep] you.
Go and see what they didn't see.
Right there.
How are you getting home?
Go now, now!
Go now!
How are you getting home?
Go
now!
She's super intoxicated.
Go now!
What do you mean, see?
... you. Go now.
Hey, officer.
Go fucking now.
Ma'am, it is, it is on video. She just walked
in front of me. And she's very nice.
I would like to press charges.
Oh, oh, oh! Yes, you know this all. Sh- go-
My name's Spencer
...
you.
Put your hands behind your
back.
Are you f- kidding me?
Are you-
Don't do that. Don't do that. Don't do that.
Please arrest. Do not
Are you f-
kidding me?
Stop. Put your hands behind your back.
Yeah, lay back.
You're f- kidding me. You're f- kidding me.
Ma'am.
Oh, oh, oh. Oh, hell no.
Hell no.
I said,
I don't want you going home
Hell no. Hell no.
Just listen to me. Just listen to me, ma'am.
I need you to listen to me for a second.
Ma'am. Go ahead. Go ahead and give it. You're
fine. No.
She's tired.
Ma'am, from this point forward, you are
officially trespassing
Oh, you're funny. You're funny.
... the safety of our property.
You're funny.
The only way you can come back to this
property-
You're funny. You're funny
... is if you're brought in by law
enforcement or medical emergency.
You're funny. You're funny.
Do you understand me?
You're funny. You're funny. Okay. You're
funny.
Well, we'll come get it. Just one second.
I have a lobby charge nurse if you need to
talk to her.
Yeah, we'll come with seven talks in a
second.
Oh, my God. You are f- kidding me. You are
not fucking kidding
me. You are f- kidding me.
Ma'am, do you have anything on you that we
need to write up?
Um, no, I don't.
All right. Anything found on you-
I don't. I have everything.
Anything found on you
No. I don't have anything!
You will have to swear that this can't-
I don't have anything!
... be considered contraband that you will
then-
God. Shut the f- up!
I will not.
I don't have any f- thing in here.
That's not freedom of speech.
Oh my God. F- you all.
F- you all. If you touch me more I'm gonna l-
need the 911.
I'll tell you right now, it's a bad f- idea,
so stop.
Okay. Okay, you're touching me-
Thank you
... way too much.
So touch... Ow! Touch me more like that.
No. You're a f-
idiot.
Go ahead and take a seat in my cruiser.
Oh, no. [laughs]
Have a seat.
Oh my God.
Put your feet in.
Oh, no. I'm not getting in here.
Yes, ma'am, you are.
No. No, I'm not.
Oh my...
Get in the vehicle now.
I don't want to.
You got battery on you. Stop.
Mm-mm. No.
So now you just fucked up.
No. I am not. I am not. I am not!
Stop.
F- get in there.
Well, now you've just got a felony, so
congratulations. It's a great idea.
Come on,
My friend.
She's going to fight me again. Just get over.
Take it easy.
Yeah.
Because she's just
And everything is not coming down with the
police.
Stop doing that. Stop.
Fuck you. F- you. F- you.
Stop. Stop.
F- you. I will f- you.
No, I will f- you.
Calm down.
Put your feet back down.
I will f- you.
Stop.
I will fuck you down.
Okay. I'm telling you right now, you're
making it worse for yourself. Stop.
Stop.
No. I'm following you down. I'm f-
you down.
Stop.
Now.
Calm down.
No, I'm not.
I'm f- you down.
Calm down.
F- you down.
You're an a- hole.
Calm down.
You're a f- hole.
Put your feet back down. Stop.
No. [laughs]
Stop.
You're f- down.
I am down.
Ma'am, please put your feet down.
Apparently the woman had been visiting her
husband at the hospital and had caused a
ruckus instead. She was clearly drunk, but
her mother will also confirm her drinking
problem. But if you think her little show
outside the hospital was bad, wait until you
watch her take it up several notches in the
back of the cop car.
Uh, battery on hospital worker and then
battery Elio.
Along with resisting.
Trespassed?
Trespassed.
They totally...
Yeah. Yeah.
Did you just leave?
Yeah.
Okay.
This is an alcohol. This, I guess is a big
bottle if you could check it and say she's
sick pasted.
Oh my God.
No, ma'am, you're under arrest. You're going
to jail.
What's her ID?
Yeah, I got it right here.
Oh, shit.
Yeah. Cool.
This is the address and I take that address
as
well, you know.
Menendez Drive...
That's the one we have right now. Okay, so
you already got her information.
The blue one.
I
appreciate it.
Where's the, uh,
the worker that was attacked by her?
The what now?
There's a worker that said he was attacked by
her.
She-
Yes. Uh-
She
pushed him.
Yeah, he had to, uh, subdue her to the
ground.
I'm gonna shine a light on him. You can just
bring him down just like that.
Can you raise your right hand real quick for
me?
[instrumental music plays] Do you swear for
me tell me the truth tonight?
Yes, sir.
I appreciate it, man. Thank you.
Thank you all for taking us. Stay safe.
Hockey knuckle bump.
Okay. Yes, sir.
Thank you. Her purse is in the back. Um, this
is her daughter but we're gonna keep the
purse is in the back. Um, this is her
daughter but we're gonna keep the purse with
her. That's what the fire said. So all right.
The problem is she framed me with this. She
can't take this to jail, so... Oh, it's
pepper spray. Oh, yeah, pass her pepper
spray. Oh, yeah, pass her pepper spray. Sure.
See, she's already asleep. That's what she
does.
She's up.
She won't be a problem for anybody.
Yeah.
Once she goes to sleep, she's fine.
Sheree. It's Mom. Sheree, baby. Wake up.
What? What?
Mom. Sweetie. Look at me.
What?
Look at me.
You have created an entire scene.
We're having to take you-
Oh, my God
... because you are drunk. You are drunk.
I'm not. I'm not.
And your hu- well, you're, you're in a police
car.
I'm not. I'm not.
You're in a police car, Sheree.
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are. What do you call this right
here? These are bars.
I got two policemen standing right behind me.
They arrested you, felony charges.
What?
You have been arrested because I, because you
wouldn't say today, "Oh, Mom, get
over here, because I'm, I think I'm gonna
drink."So now we
got a problem.
What's your problem?
So you better wake up and smell the coffee.
I'm telling you young lady, I don't know what
else to say to you.
This is ridiculous.
You hit somebody! They filed charges against
you.
What?
I'm telling you, she just, she doesn't know.
She is like-
Hmm.
When she's up, when she... What she does is
she goes to sleep and then she's fine.
You know what, I don't even drink. [laughs]
How did I end up with child support?
Oh my gosh. No, we are not.
I don't even get it.
That's the-
It, it just happened so quickly.
That's the thing is that [sighs] when
somebody becomes an adult they make their own
decisions and they're responsible for them.
And when they do, and you're, you're talking
to an old counselor who
Please tell me this is a joke.
Uh-
[laughs]
No, no.
Please tell me this is a joke.
But, I do... I am kicking myself because when
she called and said he was here,
I said, "Well, just tell me if..." Because
he's had pancreatitis and I said-
Her, her husband.
Her husband.
Yes. Please tell me this is a joke.
But nobody called. And so I kept thinking,
"Well, she's all right and they'll have her
call." Now please tell me this is a joke.
All right. Well, we're gonna get out of here.
Okay.
I need your phone.
Please tell me you didn't call the police and
let me go and
take care of my husband.
I'm begging you.
No, ma'am.
You're going to jail.
Oh no.
You committed a crime.
Why am I going to jail?
I didn't commit a crime.
Yes, you did.
No, I didn't.
There's video footage of all of it.
Oh my gosh. What is it?
You kicked an officer twice and then you
grabbed one of the nurses inside of the
hospital. Those are both crimes.
What do you mean I did that?
Along with that, you refused to leave the
hospital after being instructed to do so.
I did not do that.
All righty.
You kicked your shoes off. I'll make sure
those come inside with you.
Excuse me?
Your shoes.
For real?
Miss Sherry, go ahead and step out of the
vehicle for me.
No. You have got to be kidding me.
Step out of the vehicle now.
Are you kidding? You're kidding, right?
No, ma'am. You're in jail now. Step out of
the vehicle.
I am not going to fucking jail.
Step out of the vehicle or I'm gonna remove
you from the vehicle.
Get out of the vehicle.
Oh, oh-
Come on.
Oh my God. Just...
Oh my God. Oh my God! What are you doing?
Literally not like...
Please, please tell me you're not-
Take a seat.
You would think that setting foot in the
hospital would make her act sane, but this
woman still can't believe that being drunk
and disorderly has consequences.
Trespass battery elliott.
Battery on hospital personnel.
You are such a bitch. No one, no one, no
one... You know what you are?
You know what you are?
I mean, you're hot.
No, you know what he's doing.
You know what you're doing.
So yeah, that's my expensive bag. [laughs]
It's gonna go in your property here at the
jail.
Oh, hell no.
Hell yes.
Yep.
Oh, that's like a
$1400
bag. You almost stole it. Y'all thought that
was all mine.
Okay, give me that shit.
No, ma'am.
Ooh, it's so pretty.
How pretty are you?
Ma'am, I don't, I don't care anything that
you have to say at this point.
You're in jail, you're under arrest.
So-
I'm good. If you touch me I will knock the
shit out of you.
Are you threatening me right now?
Yeah, I will knock the shit out of you.
You will knock the shit out of me?
Yes, I will. [laughs]
All right. I'll make sure the judge sees
that.
Oh, really? So y'all don't even care about
that shit?
What? Care about what? You the one that
brought him down here. Who put it?
You already did 1/2 a day before.
Oh my God. No. I, I am done with this shit.
My husband is here for me.
Get this shit off of me.
Mm-hmm.
My husband is here for me.
He's not here, he's in the hospital.
Yes... No, my husband is here for me. Get
this shit off of me.
Take a seat.
Get this shit off of me.
Sit back down.
[laughs]
I said, "Sit the bitch down." [laughs]
Oh, you expect me to go and do that?
Yes, ma'am.
No. Get this shit off of me.
They'll take your handcuffs off, I'm not.
Get this shit off of me. Why are y'all such
fucking cows?
You are such fucking cows. No,
no.
Oh, oh, oh, help me-
Take a seat.
Help. Help me up.
You're not getting back up.
Oh, fuck you.
You're gonna stay down.
Fuck you, get your fuck off of my shit.
[punching sounds] Oh my God.
Do not kick me.
Do not kick me, do you understand?
I'ma help you up now.
Get up.
[bleep] I'm not going to
jail.
You are. The officer said King County Jail.
I am not in jail.
We're not at the Hilton's.
I'm not in jail.
Yeah, you are.
Okay. Please stop.
I'm about to take the ring off. I can't have
you hearing-
Please stop!
Oh, God.
Here we go. Just chill out.
No, ma'am. No, ma'am. I've never been through
this before.
Oh my gosh. You got like a huge guy over
there.
Oh my gosh.
Are you married?
No, I am not married.
I am scared now.
What? What does he doing
here?
I don't know.
Okay.
What is he doing here?
Did everything correctly on this? Yes, ma'am.
She was charged with battery, trespassing,
disturbing the peace and resisting an
officer. Do you think these suspects had it
coming? Let us know down in the comments.
And if you enjoyed that video, don't forget
to hit the like button and turn on
notifications so you don't miss the next one.
Most importantly, stay safe out there.