So, he's gonna have custody of my [censored]
baby?
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Some parents just don't know how to parent.
Today, we'll uncover a few of the most
disturbing moments caught on police body cam,
where parents' actions left a trail of chaos,
fear, and danger for their
own children.
I've worked so hard, man.
Well, you gotta make better decisions, dude.
I don't care how hard you work.
From neglectful parents to downright violent
ones, these stories will make you question
what some people are capable of. Stay tuned.
Are you okay?
[crying] I took a little bit, like, I don't
know-
Took a little bit of what?
It's just nervous, so-
Oh, [censored] .
The kid doesn't need to see this.
I was sleeping, man. I don't know what you
guys want from me.
Well, I just want the truth.
Many things have put these kids' lives in
danger today. Not just one thing.
Today, we have Detective Dale here to walk us
through five intense and harrowing cases
where officers arrived at the scene just in
time. Let's dive in.
I want to see my baby! That's all I want!
On August 3rd, 2024, in Ohio, officers rushed
to the scene
after getting a call about a heated fight
between a couple that quickly got out of
hand. Hold on, hold on. Where is she at?
Where is she at?
In the basement.
Lead us to her.
Get out of my house!
Stay right here. Stop. When the officers
arrived, the man was visibly shaken and fed
up. He told officers the suspect was
upstairs, acting out of control.
Under the influence after days of non-stop
use, despite his desperate pleas for
her to stop. She had taken his truck without
permission, and now this was the third time
she had turned violent. He made it clear that
he wanted her arrested, but before the
officers went up, he warned them she was
going to lie.
Do you think the officers will be able to
handle someone this unpredictable?
What's going on, brother?
There's
a woman upstairs.
Okay.
Well, what happened, man?
She's on bars. And she's extremely [censored]
up.
All right.
She's driving intoxicated right now. You'll
see it as soon as you look in her eyes.
She has my truck. Yes, she bought it, but
it's in my name, so technically that's my
truck, right?
You guys are married?
No.
No?
Have you guys lived together for a while?
Yeah.
You got kids together?
Okay.
But even... [clears throat]
By law, it's actually both of your trucks.
But it's in m- my name.
In Ohio, that doesn't matter. If, if you're,
uh, in, like, a common law relationship-
Well-
... which is basically you guys have lived
together for a while, you have kids together,
you guys have lived together for a while, you
have kids together, you know, all that sort
of jazz.. Well, I have two kids in the house-
Mm-hmm
... and she's being like that in front of two
kids.
I definitely get it, man.
She's on her third domestic violence charge.
I would like her to go to jail tonight for
domestic violence charge. I would like her to
go to jail tonight for domestic violence.
Okay, yeah. We'll try and find her, uh... And
before you get here, she's gonna say that I
kicked this bookshelf over, which I didn't.
And I have my 13-year-old daught- my
12-year-old daughter in here that can come
down here and tell you the exact same thing.
But I'm not bull- [censored] . I live right
here. Yes, I see.
Okay.
Yeah. You got a red mark in there.
And she's gonna tell you that, uh, I put my
hands on her, and my daughter will definitely
tell you that, uh, I put my hands on her, and
my daughter will definitely tell you, no, I
did not. So, tell me what happened tonight.
Tell me, like, a, like, a story, like...
Uh, I've been trying to get her to stop
eating Xanaxes for
three days.
She said she was going down to her grandma's
to do something, which she went and got more
Xanaxes.
Then she said she was gonna go do something,
then she went and got more Xanaxes and then
hid them from me. And when I told her it was
either the Xanaxes or me, she
went irate. Like I said, I can show you the
bookshelf that she kicked over.
Mm-hmm.
What's today? Saturday?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, she'll be in there all weekend.
Yeah, I definitely want her in jail for
domestic violence. Okay. Um, do you know
where she might be going?
No, she's running around hiding from you
guys.
And if she does happen to go to jail, is
there any way you can possibly get my keys
and bring them to me? Yeah, if we, uh, if we
get her, um, we'll give you a call and then-
Because I have two sleeping keys in the hou-
kids in the house. I can't get to 'em.
We could drive the keys back to you. We could
probably, like, park it somewhere and then
drive the keys back to you. We could
drive the keys back to you. We could probably
, like, park it somewhere and then drive the
keys back to you. We could probably , like,
park it somewhere and then drive the keys
back to you. We could probably , like, park
it somewhere and then drive the keys back to
you. We could probably , like, park it
somewhere and then drive the keys back to
somewhere and then drive the keys back to you
. We could probably , like, park it somewhere
and then drive the keys back to you. We could
probably , like, park it somewhere and then
drive the keys back to you. We could probably
, like, park it somewhere and then drive the
keys back to you. We could probably , like,
park it somewhere and then drive the keys
back to you. We could probably , like, park
it somewhere and then drive the keys back to
you. We could probably , like, park it
somewhere and then drive the keys back to
somewhere and then drive the keys back to you
. We could probably , like, park it somewhere
and then drive the keys back to you. We could
probably , like, park it somewhere and then
drive the keys back to you. We could probably
, like, park it somewhere and then drive the
keys back to you. We could probably , like,
park it somewhere and then drive the keys
back to you. We could probably , like, park
it somewhere and then drive the keys back to
you. We could probably , like, park it
somewhere and then drive the keys back to
somewhere and then drive the keys back to you
. We could probably , like, park it somewhere
and then drive the keys back to you. We could
probably , like, park it somewhere and then
drive the keys back to you. We could probably
, like, park it somewhere and then drive the
keys back to you. We could probably , like,
park it somewhere and then drive the keys
back to you. We could probably , like, park
it somewhere and then drive the keys back to
you. We could probably , like, park it
somewhere and then drive the keys back to
somewhere and then drive the keys back to you
. We could probably , like, park it somewhere
and then drive the keys back to you. We could
probably , like, park it somewhere and then
drive the keys back to you. We could probably
, like, park it somewhere and then drive the
keys back to you. We could probably , like,
park it somewhere and then drive the keys
back to you. We could probably , like, park
it somewhere and then drive the keys back to
you. We could probably , like, park it
somewhere and then drive the keys back to
somewhere and then drive the keys back to you
. We could probably , like, park it somewhere
and then drive the keys back to you . We
could probably , like, park it somewhere and
then drive the keys back to you . We could
probably , like, park it somewhere and then
drive the keys back to you . We could
probably , like, park it somewhere and then d
rive the keys back to you . We could probably
, like, park it somewhere and then drive the
keys back to you . We could probably , like,
park it somewhere and then drive the keys
back to you . We could probably , like, park
it somewhere and then drive the keys back to
you, dr- I can, like, drop 'em off at your
house and then you'll just go get the car
later if you need to. I mean, you can, you
throw 'em right in the back seat of that car.
I mean, you can, you throw 'em right in the
back seat of that car. I don't care. Okay.
She thought I was playing, but I'm not. This
is the third time she's put her hands on me,
and any man, even you, I know you're a cop,
but if a female puts her hands on you three
times very violently, you're gonna, you're
gonna do something, right? Right. The next
morning, when officers returned to arrest
her, they found it wasn't just herself she
was putting in danger. Things had gotten
extreme. Hey, man, where's she at? Still back
at it. Where's she at, though? Right now?
Hold on, hold on. Where's she at? Where is
she at, though? Right now? Hold on, hold on.
Where's she at? Where is she at, though?
Right now? Hold on, hold on. Where's she at?
Where is she at, though? Right now? Hold on,
hold on. Where's she at? Where is she at,
though? Right now? Hold on, hold on. Where's
she at? Where is she at, though? Right now?
Hold on, hold on. Where's she at? Where is
she at? Where is she at, though? Right now? H
old on, hold on. Where's she at? Where is she
at? In the basement. Lead us to her. You
don't have any weapons inside, do you? I
mean, yes, but none on us. Okay. I don't- Do
you have any dogs? Uh, out back. They're out
back? But- They're not inside? No, but
apparently I'm the one going to jail 'cause
I'm the aggressor. Well, we'll deal with
that. We'll deal with that in a second,
buddy. I know, I know. Okay. She doesn't have
any weapons in the basement. She has access
to the- Hey, Destiny? Yes? What's going on?
Okay, so he will not leave me alone. Okay.
I'm sorry, I'll try- Who's he to you? Um, he
is my fiance, so this is- Okay ... why I
don't want to... Be careful with my boobs.
So, this is what, um, he did to me. Um, it's
kind of easier to take it off. That's okay.
We can, we can deal with that with the medic.
Just- Yeah, yeah. We have a medic waiting for
you. Keep your shirt on right now, okay?
Okay, you can see right here, the bruise.
Okay. Oh, my God, it hurts so bad. It's just
on your bruise? Okay. Um, he's... Like, my
legs right here. Okay. Um, uh- Okay, go ahead
and put your cigarette out, okay? I'm sorry.
The, the back of my leg right here. Hold on,
baby. I know, I know. Come here, come here,
come here, come here. Hold on, hold on, hold
on. Wait, wait, wait. Here we go. Hold on,
hold on, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Here we
go. Hold on, hold on. Eh, it's okay. Let's
just get this off of here. You're gonna be c-
handcuffs right now, okay? No! Just while
we're figuring things out. But he's the one
who attacked me. [baby cries]
W- we'll get that.
We'll get it, okay? We'll get it in a minute.
Can I get a drink, please, first?
What? Go ahead.
Take a drink.
Maria, take a drink and then we're gonna
explain this to you.
[baby crying]
Yeah, set that down. Set that down.
You see my badge, right?
Yeah.
See how I lit, right?
All right, we had an accident yesterday and
it's all in the report.
All her marks are from the accident, but she
says was from me.
She's highly intoxicated.
On what?
Xanaxes. And if you look at her, you could
tell.
Okay. Did you smoke any marijuana tonight
too?
Yeah, I smoked marijuana, yes.
Oh, I don't- I don't care about it. I was
just wondering if she did as well.
Yeah. No. All she's-
Make sure to like, subscribe-
Subscribe
... and hit that notification bell so you
never miss another intense case like this.
Can I please put everything in my purse,
please?
Just stop. [baby cries]
I don't want him to have anything in my
purse, please.
Okay. We'll deal with that, but in the
meantime, hold still.
No, no, no. I'm sorry. My fingering thing on
my pinky looks like they're gonna take it
away. There you go. Hold still.
Ow, ow. Okay, okay, just like this?
That's, that's why I say yeah, there you go.
Okay. Can you please put my purse, uh, my
phone in my purse?
Oh, yeah.
Officers took her into custody, but do you
think the story just ends here?
Definitely not.
Hey, Jessie. Will you talk to this officer
for me?
This is the other per- This is the other-
Give it to him, okay?
The cops are here and I need you to explain
exactly what's going on.
Can my baby please not stay with him? He's
very violent.
Well, he's D- he's dad, right?
Yes, but I-
He's the biological dad?
Yes, but I have five other people ready to
come get her.
Okay.
Okay. Well, we're gonna figure that out in a
minute, okay?
Okay. Yes. Yes, sir. Yes, ma'am.
Okay. Is that her stuff? [phone rings]
Yep.
Keep walking. Keep walking.
Oh, God. Oh, G- Oh, God. We just had physical
therapy on our backs-
Yep
... like, for eight days in a row and, like,
we got some big settlement and, like-
Okay
... a company truck hit us.
Okay.
Oh, I can't... Can you help me? I'm sorry.
Yep. Keep going.
Okay. Oh, God. Oh, my God.
I got you.
Oh, my gosh. Okay.
There you go. Come over this way, ma'am.
Can I see number one sec?
Nope. We're gonna keep moving. Come on.
Okay.
Because we have a seat for you and we want to
get you checked out, okay?
Yeah, thanks a lot for you beating my ass.
We're gonna have lunch.
Will you do me a huge favor? Just move to
that side of the bed for me.
Oh, oh, oh sorry.
Just leave it. Just move to that side of the
bed.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No, no, no. Come on.
I got it.
Okay.
I'm just gonna-
Can you
help me please? Can you, like, leave me?
Yeah.
Like, can I call my landlord?
What? You guys both stay in here, right? Come
on, step on down.
Yes-
Let's go. Come on.
... but we don't have a lease.
Okay.
Like, our landlord, our last lease-
But that doesn't matter right now, okay?
Because you guys are both staying here, so
there's-
So, I don't-
... occupant residency, okay?
I'm not trying to be rude. I'm very sorry.
I know. No.
But I'm not understanding why I'm going to
jail when he didn't do-
You're going to jail for a separate incident.
It's not this incident.
For what?
You're not going to jail for this.
For what am I going to jail for?
Uh, we're gonna explain that to you in a
minute, okay?
Is there any way they could de-cuff from the
front? Like, I promise I won't run. I'm too
cold. We can't cuff it in the front. I got to
do the same thing every time for everybody-
Okay
... but if you have a seat, medics will come
take a look at you.
You know how long it's gonna be?
Yeah.
So I'd be in jail?
No. I'll- I'm gonna explain it. We're gonna
fig- We got a bunch of things to figure out,
okay? So we're gonna, we're gonna look at a
few things, okay, ma'am? So the medic's right
here. I'm gonna have you sit down and then
you can talk to him and tell him what's going
on, okay? This is like butt first or...
Just, yep, butt first.
Yep, bring your leg up.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God. I can't, I can't,
I can't.
Come on. I gotta help you.
Okay, hold on. Hold on. Oh, my God, my nail.
My nail, my nail.
Oh, oh, no, no, no. Oh, no. Oh, my pinky
nail.
Okay, okay.
There you go. You're fine.
Okay, okay, okay. [sighs]
Okay.
So explain to this officer what's, what's
going on. You requested one, correct?
Yeah. So pretty much I was trying to get away
from the situation and my
fiance-
Okay
... took my daughter out of the stroller,
took her back in the house.
I was gone all night taking care of my
grandma because she has asthma and she was
having a very bad episode. And he literally,
all's he said was, "If you don't
come home, I'm calling the cops. I got videos
of you doing this and you doing that." No, he
doesn't. There's only one camera and I
unhooked it and I took the wire with me.
Okay.
But he said, "If you don't come home and talk
to me right now, then I'm calling the cops
and talk to me right now, then I'm calling
the cops and you're going to jail, blah,
blah, blah, blah." He literally said, "If you
don't come home right now, blah, blah, blah-
Okay ... then I won't call the cops and then
we can just sit down and talk." He's acting
like a big child. Okay.
But he literally did this to my legs, like,
my back-
What's, what's up with your neck? What,
what... did what to your legs?
Do you want me to stand up and show you or-
Well, you can just show us right here. Just
start pointing, okay?
You can point on this shoulder right here,
it's very bruised. Um, all around my neck.
Like,
my back is very scratched up. Like, and he
did all of this.
The only thing I did to him was when he
pushed me into a corner, like, he
face-pushed me into a corner, the one in
there, as soon as you go in, um, where the
crystal shelf is, he, like, grabbed my face
and pushed me into the corner and then I,
like, pushed him back from me and my hand
did, like-
Okay
... push his throat and I said, "Get the f-
off of me."
Okay.
So that is the only time I ever touched him.
Got it. Okay.
But other than that, he literally just, like,
would not stop touching me, throwing me on
the bed. Like, "No, you [censored] . You're
not leaving." Like, "You're not driving off
in the car. That's our car. You're not doing
this."
Okay.
[sighs] He, like, literally just would not
let me leave and I was like, "I just need
time away from you. I need time to think.
I don't want to be with you."
When did all this happen?
This happened, uh, last night was when it got
really bad, but the day before-
Okay
... was when I had to go spend the night with
my grandma-
Okay
... to do that.
Okay.
And then he was like, "Really? You're gonna
spend all night with your grandma instead of
sleeping in bed with me?" And his daughter
that is, like, 12 years
old-
So really quick-
... 11
... really quick, Destiny, okay? Hold on,
Destiny. Hold on.
Uh-huh.
What do you need these gentlemen here to
check on you? You called them here. You
requested they come here. I just want, like,
my back, like, my legs, like, they just hurt
so bad. Like, I can barely walk. Like, my, my
toe right there, my pinky, like, everything
hurts so bad. Like, I'm in physical therapy.
We're supposed to go today.
We're supposed to go eight days in a row for,
like, a company truck hit
us.And we're supposed to get, like, this big
settlement.
And, um, they do the waterbed thing and the
massage thing and everything else.
Okay.
And, um, it's getting, like, a little bit
better, but, like, it hurts so [censored]
bad. And, like, my back is just, like-
She stated she took at least 16-
... killing me and, like, I just-
... Xanax. Her, her, her eyes are pretty pink
though, so that's why I was
... I don't understand why he, like, he keeps
barking at me.
Destiny, have you taken anything today?
No.
You haven't taken nothing?
No. No.
No pills? Xanax?
No.
You haven't been drinking?
No. He keeps saying that, but no. He is
taking Xanaxes, he is drinking, he is taking
pain pills.
Okay.
His mom gets pain pills and Xanaxes, the
peach footballs
and, uh, cocaine, and he goes over there
every day and snorts them with her.
Okay.
Is there any way you'll look at my back and
see if it's really bad?
Okay, please help her.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, just please be easy, easy, easy.
Here, step on out, okay?
Okay.
I'm not gonna, I'm not gonna let you fall
far.
[knocking]
Oh, God. Oh, no, no, my butt, my butt, oh,
God, oh, God, okay.
Well, I mean, they are hard plastic and a
little bit-
Hold on, sorry, a little wedgie.
Ow, ow, ow, okay.
Yep. Okay, go ahead turn in and face in,
okay?
Sure.
This, this gentleman here is gonna look at
ya.
So, I don't understand why he's not going to
jail too if he's the one who beat my ass.
So, you just got a little soft abrasion right
here. That's gonna heal on its own.
You don't need to worry about that, okay?
You said that's fresh? Maybe.
But can you look at his back?
Maybe. Yeah.
Like his back is way less worse than mine.
Mine's way worse.
Okay.
Like, the whole thing is, is I was b-
I was gone last night, and he got mad-
Okay. Yeah
... that I wouldn't come home-
Okay
... and he called the cops.
I understand.
And he got his 11-year-old daughter-
Okay
... to lie for him and say that-
... I smacked him-
Okay
... or scratched him, and she was sleeping.
Okay. So, right now, you're gonna take a seat
back in. They can't do anything else for you
right now, you're gonna take a seat back in.
They can't do anything else for you right
here, okay? Okay. Is there any way- We're all
gonna explain all this, okay?
Okay. [police radio chatter]
There you go.
Oh, God.
Yep. Go ahead and move your feet in right
now.
Is there any way-
Yep, move your feet in
... oh, I can pee before I go?
No, you're gonna have to hold it.
I'm gonna pee-
Okay? I'm, I'll make sure we get this
through, okay? We're gonna put this right
here. But can my baby please go with my,
my family and not him? He's very abusive.
He smacks the baby and throws her in her bed,
and, like, he's very abusive.
Okay.
Like, he literally-
Well, we're gonna, we're gonna double check,
okay?
He lit-
We're gonna look at, like I said, we're gonna
look at a few things-
He literally-
... and then we'll see what we're doing.
... threw her across the room.
Okay. Okay.
While officers were questioning her fiance
and getting evidence from her daughter, she
gave them a hard time.
Excuse me. Excuse me. [knocking] I'm so
sorry, I'm just so hot.
Ma'am, it's okay. Just listen for a second.
It-
Is there, is there any way you could turn the
air up?
What? What?
Just hang tight with her.
Yes.
So,
okay. So, what, so are you guys both living
here together?
Yeah, but I plan on moving.
What happened this morning? Why, why did you
call us here?
Uh, because she came back home and she was
still
irate. She was still on Xanaxes and she told
me to call
you. She said, she said she was gonna call
you guys because I beat her ass-
Okay.
... with
So nothing physical happened between you guys
this morning? All that stuff happened last
night? She just came back?
No, this,
this happened this morning.
Okay. What's that from, buddy?
Her, her pushing me away and me trying to
walk away.
Okay. Wha-
And-
Okay. What's that from?
And her punching me in my mouth.
This morning?
Yes.
Okay.
And last night, uh, your other officer should
have documentation of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm, I'm gonna check that
too.
They, they took pictures.
Okay. Perfect.
Because I tried to get her put in jail last
night.
Okay. [knocking]
God damn!
I can't hear you, ma'am. What?
I, this is hurting my shoulder, this
seatbelt.
Can you pull it down just a little bit this
way, please? And I'm really, really hot.
I don't, I don't understand what you're
referring-
Like, can you pull it, like, over, like, just
down, like, right there?
And-
Yeah
... can you please turn the air on?
The, the air is on.
It's all the way up?
Yeah, it's running. [door opening]
So, he's gonna have custody of my [censored]
baby?
Um, was your daughter, uh, your older
daughter awake for everything that happened
this morning? Yeah, yeah, that's why I would
like you to talk to her.
Would you mind going up and speaking with her
real quick for me?
Yep.
Okay. [knocking]
[coughing]
[radio playing]
[laughing]
Um, she put her, she put her hands on you and
there was, like, a big,
like, red mark on your back. And I was in
front of you.
I was, like, right there, and
there was, like, a bunch of yelling and
stuff.
Did she also throw the fan at me?
Yeah.
Did I put my hands on her whatsoever?
Nope. And there was a shelf that she kicked
outside that she broke.
Thank you for talking to me, okay?
We're leaving today, baby. You don't have to
deal with this no more.
Thank God.
Mom's probably gonna go to jail.
Okay.
Why the [censored] does the abuser person get
to get my [censored]
baby? [crying] This is [censored]
bullshit.
The person who beats the [censored] out of
me, I go to jail because
y'all wanna believe him
because I wasn't here. Excuse me?
[knocking]
Can I at least get a tissue or something in
here and say bye to my baby?
Hold on. We have a lot of things we're
figuring out real quick.
Okay, but-
Okay?
I'm like, I'm like drooling everywhere.
Okay. Hold on a minute, okay?
As officers arrested her, she broke down
crying, begging to see her baby and
accusing her fiance of lying. Despite the
chaos, officers stayed calm,
confirmed her warrants and let her kiss her
child goodbye before jail.
Why? Because he's the one who beats me.
Stay in there. Stay in there.
No, don't tell him to kiss you.
Put your leg in there. Put your leg in there.
You're hurting me!
No, I'm not. [knocking]
What are you doing? [hand slapping]
Stop.
You're gonna get charged with vandalism.
You're gonna get a felony.
I want to see my baby. That's all I want.
I want to give her a kiss, she's crying.
Can you not do-
Bout to call the mother in.
Maybe, as you know, you won't because I'm
being a bitch.
[hand slapping]
I wanna say one thing to him and I wanna see
my baby before I go.
No.
I will never be with you again.
Fuck you! [hand slapping]
Yeah, you must... They must not have been
tight.
Hold on a minute.
Hey-
I'm not putting them back on until I see my
baby.
So here's the deal. This is gonna... No.
Step-
I want my baby out.
Turn around.
No, I want my baby.
Turn away from me.
Turn around and face me.
No.
Are you really gonna go this route?
I want to give my baby a kiss and then I will
cry, please.
So that's not how this works, okay? You're
going to jail, for instance, that happens
five more times- I will never be with you
again.
Stop.
Never! Get out of my house!
Stay right here. Stop. You wanna see your
child or not?
Ow, you're hurting me.
I'm not. I am not hurting you.
Yes, you are. You are hurting me. My
shoulder!
It hurts! You put it on to stay off of this
shoulder.
Goddamn! Justin, don't ever fucking ask to be
with me again.
Go to your fucking mom.
Stop.
I just want... Ow!
Can you untie these, please?
No.
'Cause of the way you're acting? Why?
I just wanna get my baby and fucking kiss.
He's gonna beat my ass when I go to jail
because I wasn't here last night
and y'all believed him.
Can you wipe this snot off my nose?
Yeah.
Come here, baby. I love you.
Oh.
Here, I'll wipe it off.
You fucking happy I never wanna be with you?
You come here, give me a kiss.
I told, I told this cop if you start, I'm
gonna take her from you.
You don't have to be with me again. You did
this, not me.
Give me a kiss. Give me a kiss. Give mommy a
kiss. Take your binky.
You have her scared.
Mwah. Yeah, because of you, I never wanna be
with you again.
Do not be here when I get back.
I won't. Neither will my kids.
Yeah, neither will fucking Joe. Joe will find
out.
Okay, I'm getting emergency custody of my
daughter.
No, you're not. I will.
No, you're not.
I'll be in jail for a day.
Hey.
Yes?
Okay. Your food stamp card.
I want that with me.
You want it with you?
Yes.
You don't want it with him-
No
... so that way he can feed your child?
No.
Okay.
He gets to sell it all.
She said no.
Okay, that's fine.
Okay. So this is the deal. Yes, you're being
arrested today.
On not only whatever they called last night.
I wasn't here so I can't attest to that, but
you did have a broadcast with us for your
events last night. But you also have two
warrants, which are both confirmed.
One out in Moraine, one out in Montgomery
County, so you're also going to jail on those
two. Are you s-
Your daughter is gonna stay with dad here,
where you guys have been living.
When you get out, if you decide you guys are
gonna separate-
We're moving in two days.
Okay.
Two days.
Well, if you guys are moving in two days,
that's fine, you can take daughter, but you
can't be living together if you guys are
gonna act like this 'cause it's-
No, I don't want-
Look, it's, it's gonna get... It's pretty
soon it's gonna get child ser- children's
services involved. No, we've already had CPS.
Okay, so you've already-
My daughter is 15 months and she has a hand-
You've already had it, so you understand?
... with a hand.
Okay, so you understand?
So I'm not gonna do warrants. I'm sorry, I
don't mean to be difficult but I'm having a
panic attack really, really bad.
What's up?
I'm having a panic attack really, really bad.
[laughs] I can't breathe. [coughing]
Hey.
I should have an inhaler. [gasping]
Where's your inhaler at?
It's in my safe. My bruise on my left
shoulder is hurting me so bad.
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
The woman ended up getting arrested for
domestic violence.
If she's found guilty, what kind of
punishment do you think would be fair?
Whatever you said, double it for this next
suspect on our list.
This case didn't just break the rules, it
went way beyond them.
Even the officers were shocked by what they
found.
Where's my son?
He's in the front seat of that car.
How?
He fell out your car.
That car?
I was sleeping.
Did the-
Where was your son at?
I was sleeping. He was on this side.
Who was driving?
On September 15th, 2021, a shocking call came
in that someone
saw a child fall out of a moving car during a
U-turn, but the car didn't
stop, it just kept going. You'll never guess
what happened next.
Where's my son?
He's in the front seat of that car.
How?
He fell out your car.
That car?
How he fell out my car?
Just walk, I don't wanna put your handcuffs
on. It's for your kids.
Just walk with us to the back of this car
like we're walking and talking.
When we clear the rear of your car, we're
gonna put you back in.
T- 10-60, 10-4
A man who saw everything explains to the
officer what happened and how a
small child tumbled out. The little
four-year-old was terrified by what
happened.
How you doing?
Hey, sir. Thanks for coming so quick.
What happened? What happened?
I've never seen anything like that. This
silver car, best I can tell it's silver.
Yeah.
Pulls around and I see the damn doors open
and this kid comes rolling out of it.
He falls out of the car?
He just came falling out of it, slide, rolls
all the way over.
And the car took off?
The car just kept rolling.
Which way did it go?
It kept going.
Silver SUV, pickup?
No, a, just a Caravan, a car. Just a car.
It's a car or what kind? Like yours?
Car. Yeah, uh, no, like a car-car. Like a
regular, [laughs] you know, sedan.
Alpha 216, Flagler.
Go ahead.
All right, I'm out with the caller. He
advised, "I have Bravo Mike juvenile, three
years old, who fell out of a silver unknown
make or model vehicle that continued-"
100 westbound
... westbound on 100." That's all I have.Did
it hit a y'all car or did...?
No, nothing like that.
My God.
10-4.
Mind if make call to my work?
Yeah, please do. [car hooting]
Older model, newer model, anything except the
stickers on it?
Older model. It didn't look new by no means.
Like I said, my truck-
Alpha 216, he's finding older model. He
didn't get a good look at the vehicle.
I meant it wasn't a new car.
Okay.
It wasn't a new car.
Is that for us to go and see?
The problem is I was just... I saw him-
Oh
... and I was in disbelief and I just got
over there.
I'm in disbelief right now. [laughs] .
Yeah. Um...
Hey, boy, are you all right, pal?
All
right.
He's got, he's got a little cut. Let me see,
buddy. Thank you.
Oh my gosh.
He's got a little cut on his finger.
Hey, do you know your name, big guy?
Come right here.
What?
Can you tell us your name, buddy?
Do you know your name, bud?
You can tell us, what's your name?
[beep] .
Hmm. Okay.
He's had a hard time telling me about
anything-
Yeah.
Um,
sorry, let me get more clear.
So the, so the ca- He came out of the front
seat or back seat?
Back seat, back right. Back right.
So the, the car came off Old Kings Road,
right?
He, he or she made a U-turn.
Made a U-turn?
Right where that white car is-
Okay
... right there. I'm sitting first one in
line over there.
Yeah.
Off 213, 10-4.
They turned and I thought it was a dent in
the door, but it was-
Albany, where are you going?
... the damn door open.
And he fell in the back?
And he just watched
Just signal 14, subject says he may have an
049 Massachusetts.
He goes boom, boom, boom, over here in the
curb.
Yeah.
And I just, I just looked at him.
And that's all you have?
Like I say, I just, silver car is all I can
think of.
Yeah.
And I just got... I kind of ran that-
Did the door close when it kept going or did
it just...
Not th- No, it was, it was still open. Um-
High rate... Was it reckless? High rate of
speed or just...
It wasn't like it was out of control.
Yeah, yeah.
It wasn't like it was burning tires or
anything.
Yeah.
Um,
I don't know. I even tried to ask him-
Holy Molly
... like did anybody know that you were out
of the car?
[laughs] . That's why I'm wondering they
don't know he fell out.
Yeah. Were you riding with your mom?
Were you riding with your mommy?
Was daddy with you too?
Just mom?
Okay.
Do you have your ID on you, sir?
I, uh, yes.
Just for our report.
Yeah, no problem.
We're not gonna get them.
Did you see how his mother came back only
after realizing too late that she had left
her four-year-old behind?
Where's my son?
He's in the front seat of that car.
He fell out your car.
10-4.
How he fell out my car?
Copy tag for the parents who just showed up.
Matt-
How did he fall out my car?
You tell, you tell me that.
10-4.
Was he buckled in?
I was sleeping.
Where was your son at?
I was sleeping. He was on this side.
Who was driving? [laughs]
My brother. He said he he-
he said he heard the door open, but he
didn't, he didn't think like-
10-4. Showing that there's no vehicle
registration to it. Registration is showing
canceled. Everybody have their IDs out, their
IDs ready?
He's in the front seat of the car. If you
wanna go get him from this gentleman.
Oh, my god. What happened?
Do you want to come get him out of this man's
car?
Is he okay?
He's o- He's got a little cut on his finger.
He's okay.
When did y'all realize he wasn't in the car?
Right now. Like right now. We got onto the
expressway and my daughter was like, "Well,
Bobby what did... Why you leave?"
It's not... Just don't, don't yell at him.
He's-
I know, I'm... It's not-
You wanna... You wanna pick him up? He's
scared.
And
his hand hurts. Okay?
Let me just, uh... [laughs]
We had, we had a crash going down on 30.
So,
this gentleman says the silver car makes the
U-turn, as they U-turn, back door opens up,
he falls out. Car continues
westbound.
The doors are locked. I don't know how.
She said she gets on the interstate and
realized their kid in the backseat.
She was sleeping, the brother was driving.
They returned to the scene.
Um, he's got a small cut on his finger. All
right. Well, appreciate it, man. You wanna...
I'll get you outta here so you won't have to
get run over. But that's all right?
Yeah.
Hey guys, I'm gonna get him outta here. Just
wanna... I'll close your door. Are you
getting all his stuff? All right. I'll get
you out with the ambulance here.
Oh, goodness. Where's everybody's car seats?
They gonna wear a seatbelt, right?
Um, well, you have... There's gonna be four
kids in that-
Nine, seven-
... only three seats.
So how-
How many seat-
How many seats? Four kids for three seats.
With three seat belts.
They all fit there.
It doesn't matter if they all fit there. How
many seat belts are there?
Oh.
There's three seat belts. Every juvenile
needs to be in a seat belt.
So obviously someone's not in a seat belt if
there's four kids.
I mean, I just got this car.
I used to have a big van, but I-
So you're saying if I, if I just get this car
and I wanna sit four kids in the backseat,
I'm gonna make sure there's four seat belts?
10-4.
So did you check to see the seat belt for the
car?
I have six kids, what do you want?
I, I know, but I understand that.
I'll take 121 victors in the Z section.
This what I was saying. This is my dream.
I understand, but-
I didn't think that my son would ever do
something like that.
10-4. Do you have your, your ID?
No.
You don't have anything?
Can I get your name?
He got my name.
He got your name?
Yeah.
All right. Have y'all been smoking?
Yeah, I've been smoking one joint.
When?
Like, a couple...
Like, couple, like 20 minutes ago.
20 minutes ago? And you're driving? Four kids
in the backseat?
I, I had window down.
You had your window down? Were you smoking in
the car?
Yeah, one time.
You were smoking in the car with them in the
back?
I had the window down though.
Do you have any more weed in the car?
No, no, no weed.
Can you step out for me so we can talk over
here?
No, but under state law,
every child needs to be in a seat belt at
least.
I know that.
At certain ages. So, how are they all in seat
belts?
I buckled them in a seat belt. Is the child
locked great?
I, I can't tell which way it's gonna, gotta
go. I also have a key in there.
I don't know which way it goes.
210.
They didn't even have the child locked in and
was smoking with kids in the car.
Can we really call them responsible parents?
Due first. Case number generated for their
area.
Can you do me a favor, sweetie? Can you try
to open this door when I close it?
[door closing] Go ahead and try to open it.
They're on now.
10-4.
They're on now. They weren't on before.
Step in the car. Yeah, come over here.
Where are you guys coming from? [alarm
beaming]
I'm coming from Florida.
Well, wait. Where in Florida? Where you head-
Where are you coming from in Florida?
Trying to get to South Carolina.
Okay. What part of Florida are you guys
coming from?
Gotta explain to the guy.
Very far away.
Okay.
Far,
far away.
Trying to get to South Carolina.
Just type them by name.
Possibly out of order for a
10-27 10-29 10-6.
This guy.
Okay.
10-4.
Can he sit back in the car?
He can sit back in the car. [car door bangs]
So, you say you were smoking in the car with
them in there?
Yeah.
Is there any more weed in the car at all?
Like, probably a joint, yeah.
A joint?
Where would that joint be at?
It's, like, in the car and
... was it, is it in the Swisher's wrapper in
the
car?
No. It's actually in the back.
In the back? [car horn honks] All right.
Do you have medical marijuana card?
Oh, no.
You don't have medical marijuana card?
So my question is, is how do you not realize
that the door opens and one of the kids fly
out and then we get on 95?
'Cause I ain't, I ain't hear anything.
[car revs]
You didn't hear the door open and shut?
I kind of did hear something that why I was
like-
And see a kid fall out of the car?
I kinda did hear something.
So you know, as the driver, you're
responsible to make sure that everyone has a
seatbelt on, right? So if there's four kids
in the back of that car and three seat belts,
how does everyone have a seatbelt on? They
didn't have seat belts on, did they? None of
them had seat belts on. I thought that they
did.
So
my question is, is if there's three seat
belts and there's four kids, how do you get
three seat belts and there's four kids, how
do you get three seat belts on four kids?
It, it's impossible 'cause there's no way to
put three seat belts on four kids.
That means one kid didn't have a seat belt on
and obviously the kid that didn't have a seat
belt on and obviously the kid that didn't
have a seat belt on is the one that flew out
the kid that didn't have a seat belt on is
the one that flew out the car and into the
road, right? I was just driving for my
sister. She was tired.
All right. At this time, you're detained. All
right, we'll talk to you in a little bit,
okay? Okay. Hey, Dessie?
Dessie?
Dessie? [car horn honks]
You're under arrest.
No... You're just detained right now, okay?
You're not under arrest at this time.
You can come out here as they come on, but
for now, you are detained because this is
what happened, okay? Oh, he's just being
detained?
Yeah. Separate to that, strong odor of
marijuana coming out of this car.
Marijuana?
Yeah. There's a strong odor of marijuana
coming out of this car, so that's why he's
detained. Go ahead to finish answering his
questions and we'll, uh, tell you what's
going on. Oh, I mean-
Finish answering his questions and get him
out of here. So few things going on.
One, how old were the kids in the back seat?
W- what age range are they from?
My daughter is nine-
Okay
... three. My other daughter is
seven.
Okay.
My son is, um-
Fire an alpha 3211. Check
... five, and Jube's four.
All right, so the four-year-old should be in
a car seat.
According to Florida law, all children age
five and younger must be restrained in a
federally approved crash... in a child
restraint device.
We're going to have to make this... This is a
booster seat, car seat, or any other
manufactured integrated child seat. So two of
them aren't in car seats. Okay?
Second thing,
four kids in the back seat, only three seat
belts available for them. That's a problem.
And the third thing is we all can smell the
marijuana coming out of the car, including
the third thing is we all can smell the
the third thing is we all can smell the marij
uana coming out of the car, including the
third thing is we all can smell the marij
uana coming out of the car, including the thi
rd thing is we all can smell the marij uana
coming out of the car, including the third
thing is we all can smell the marij uana
thing is we all can smell the marij uana comi
ng out of the car, including the third thing
is we all can smell the marij uana coming out
of the car, including the third thing is we
all can smell the marij uana coming out of
the car, including the third thing is we all
can smell the marij uana coming out of the
car, including the third thing is we all can
smell the marij uana coming out of the car,
including the third thing is we all can smell
the marij uana coming out of the car,
including the thi rd thing is we all can
smell the marij uana coming out of the car,
including the Paramedics and the
firefighters. How is this related to fire
fighters? So we'll look into those three
things right now. How are you doing, sir? So
hang tight while we finish doing what we're
doing. How many of you went to a 911 on Lake
15th? That's my 30 year wedding anniversary.
Is there any marijuana in this car, do you
know? All right. Well- You can check it. ...
w- well, we e- with or without your
permission, just the smell of marijuana alone
give us the right to check your car. So
that's what deputy- Wait. Where, where, where
are we? I don't even know- You're in Palm
Coast, Florida, probably about half hour
north of Daytona. All right. Ma'am, I'm gonna
have to talk to you for a little bit now,
okay? You mind coming over here with me so we
can talk? Just to the front of his car. And
the front of his car. And the pills I found
in the glove box, the Xanax bars? The Xanax?
Yeah, those are my anxiety pills. Okay. Are
those pre- I know, I know- Do you have a
prescription? I don't have it in my, um,
bottle. No, I don't have my prescription. Do
you have a prescription for Xanax in
particular? Um,
they give me, um,
some type of pills like th- that's for like
that.
Has, has that doctor prescribed Xanax for us
too? That's what we're asking.
Um-
'Cause we, we can check that. We can go onto
the record we can check to see.
No, not yet. No.
So he hasn't prescribed you any Xanax before?
But they, they prescribed me with pills that
are like in the Xanax family type.
In the Xanax family?
Yeah.
But he hasn't prescribed you those, those
pills?
No.
Where'd you get those pills?
Because I have bad anxiety pills. I mean,
anxiety problems.
What, where did you get those pills from?
My friend gave 'em to me.
Your friend gave you those pills?
Yeah.
Okay.
I take it for my anxieties that I had.
Does your friend have a prescription for the
pills?
My, my sister.
Is it his, is it his prescription?
Probably, probably he has a prescription of
them. I don't know.
Probably. Okay.
'Cause my sister passed away and, um,
not too long ago, so I, I'm dealing with like
anxieties and stuff.
So I would have to take-
That's what I'm saying though, if, if you got
anxiety, that's when you go to the doctor and
the doctor and the doctor prescribe you the
medication and stuff.
Yeah.
But getting it from-
If you see the bottles right there, you can
probably see the old ones that I have right
there. So, the, the secondary con-
I've been trying to go to the doctor.
The, the secondary concern that I have is,
when you guys left Miami- Okay ...
okay, you got four, four children in the back
seat.
Um-
I have six kids
They're,
they're ages on the back seat right now, is
it five, or nine, five, four and three?
That's, that's our ages in the back seat?
Uh-huh.
Uh.
Um, yeah, nine.
Five.
Seven.
Seven. Nine, seven?
Five and four.
Five and four. Okay. So under Florida law,
uh,
and y- do you have driver's license in
Florida?
No, I have to get one. They just started
giving them to people.
So you don't have a driver's license from
Florida? Okay.
Well, it's, it's [car horn honks]
law that states that any juvenile that's in a
vehicle that's under the age of five needs to
be in a car seat. On top of that, any
juvenile that's under the age of 18 needs to
have a seatbelt on. All right, so the, the
problem is, is these cars are designed for,
for three passengers in the rear seat. Right
now, we have four passengers in the rear
seat. Right now, we have four passengers in
the rear seat. Okay? Oh, my God.
So,
it, it, the car is legally not allowed to
travel with four juveniles.
Even four adults in the back seat, you
couldn't travel with four adults in the back
seat if you want to. Because everyone has to
have the option to be able to sit with a seat
belt, even as an adult, you don't have to sit
with a seatbelt in the back seat, you still
have to sit with a seatbelt in the back seat,
you still have to have that option. [car
revs] But like I said, the main concern is,
is that we left Miami, we put four juveniles
in the back seat, and obviously one of the
juveniles didn't have a seatbelt on. Because
you got three seat belts- We had two. Yeah,
I'm, I'm still saying, I'm still saying-
Three seat belts-
I'm still saying-
And four juveniles, that leaves someone out
from getting it. And obviously, the one
that... I don't, I don't know why the door
opened, I don't know if he had hit the door
or if it was a malfunction of the door. I see
that there's damage on that side of the car.
Yeah, there's a mess on this side.
So with, with the damage on the side of the
car, maybe the door lock's not working
properly. I, I, I don't know that, and I'm
not a mechanic.
But all I know is that-
By simple math,
three seat belts, four juveniles, and one
juvenile falls out, that's most likely the
one juvenile falls out, that's most likely
the one that wasn't wearing the seat belt.
Okay?
So that's, that's the concern that I have.
The secondary concern is, um, who was the
male that was driving the car?
My little brother.
That's your little brother? Okay. Um, were
you awake when your brother was smoking
marijuana in the car? No.
No, you weren't awake when he was-
I was sleeping. That's why-
Okay, you were sleeping when he was smoking
marijuana? Did you know that he had marijuana
on him? Uh, no. I wasn't aware that he had
marijuana on him.
Okay, so you weren't aware that he had
marijuana?
How much, how much marijuana he had?
Uh, it doesn't matter if it's, if it's an
ounce or 10 ounces, it's still not legal to
have marijuana with you. And then obviously
it's not... If, if he smoked it 20 minutes
ago, it's, it's not legal to-
I don't know. I don't know when he smoked it.
I don't know if he smoked it when he stopped
here. I don't know. I was sleeping.
Get's back on the road, and now he's driving
under the influence of a narcotic [horn
honks] with four juveniles. One of 'em
obviously not in a seat. I can't, I can't say
that they all weren't in seat belts. I know
that when we came up to the car, they weren't
in seat belts. I know that when we came up to
the car, they weren't in their seat belts.
But, um, two of 'em were supposed to be in
car seats. Which ones? Like you said, I
thought you said the four-year-old was
supposed to be in the car seat. So anybody
under the age of five needs to be in a car
seat. Under eight?
Five and under. Five and under has to be in a
car seat.
So two out of the four kids should've been
in- Car seats ... federally approved car
seats. The officer grows more concerned. He
points out that not only was the driver
unlicensed, but the kids weren't wearing seat
belts.
There were no child safety seats, and there
may have been drugs in the car.
Trying to avoid making a scene in front of
the kids, the officers calmly ask her to
walk to the back of the car, where they
quietly detain her.
Your brother,
do you mind running him up to South Carolina
to go meet his dad?
Or bring his dad back so that he can see his
kid?
All that. That would be stuff that
I would expect a parent to do, um, for their
children to make sure that their children are
safe. Okay? Um, do you have any family that's
in the area here? Where is your family at?
Far away. We don't live here at all.
I, I understand you don't live here, but
where would your family be at?
Where would the nearest relative be at?
Very far. Miami, Florida. And nobody have a
car.
And nobody has a car down in Miami? They
don't know anybody that could-
No.
Okay.
I just got my car. And this car is not even
under my name.
I h- I was gonna do all the registration and
everything, um, on the... Today, the 15th?
Yeah.
Today. Whenever I get back to Miami with my
brother. My brother's the one with the
license. My older brother.
Your older brother's the one with the
license?
And-
But he had to go to work.
Your older brother had to go to work?
He stayed.
Okay. So your younger brother, does he have a
license?
He never had a license before.
So your younger brother never had a license
before?
He's not been suspended or anything like
that.
Okay, so did you know he didn't have a
license?
Um,
I think I... Yeah, I thought... Yeah, he
didn't... I don't think... Yeah, he didn't
have a license. No. Okay. So that, that's the
other concern that I have, is now you're
asking your little brother to drive you
knowing that-
I never-
Knowing that he doesn't have a license-
Right
... and you're putting your children on the
back of the car who don't have seat belts on
a non-licensed driver.
Listen, I love all of my kids. I understand
what you're saying.
I'm not... This isn't a question of if you
love your kids or not. Okay?
I know I...
This-
What happened was a mistake. I understand. I
don't know what you want me to do.
There's, there's a lot [laughs] I want you to
do as a mom to, to, for the safety of your,
for the safety of your, for your children.
Okay, I can go buy a car seat. I can, I can
go buy a car seat. I can, I can go buy a car
seat. But at that right now, I don't care.
Okay. At this time, we're gonna detain you.
All right?
Over here?
Yes. No, do this, Edward. Do this. Walk with
us. Walk to the back. Just walk. Walk, walk
to the back. Just walk. Walk, walk to that
car. We're just gonna walk to the back of the
car so you can close the door and hand cuffs
on. So it's not... I don't wanna do it in
front of your kids. So walk with us to the
back of this patrol car. How am I gonna get
outta jail here? Yeah. Walk to the back of
this patrol. We're not detaining you. We're
not detaining you. We're not putting you in
jail. We're detaining you, okay? Just walk. I
don't wanna put your handcuffs in front of
your kids. Just walk with us to the back of
this car like we're walking and talking. When
we clear the rear of your car, we're gonna
put your handcuffs on. Miami Beach 10-1569
10-4 11-57.
I'll explain it all in a second. I'm gonna
explain it in a second.
Keep walking with us like we're talking, and
once we rear this car, we're gonna, we're
gonna- Miami 12-30, reference A-
... put you in the back of a patrol car. I
don't wanna do it in front of your kids. Just
walk with us. Green Subaru Legacy. Whiskey
Mike Watch.
Come right here.
Do you know you have a 12-year-old possibly
driving?
I'm gonna tell you, I'm gonna tell you why.
Vehicle going eastbound on North Second.
All right. At this point we're detaining you.
Go ahead and put your hands behind your back.
But I was sleeping, man.
20 minutes, 21 minutes.
Why you gotta do this?
'Cause there's many things going on here.
Many things, not just one.
Many things that put these kids' lives on
danger today. Not just one thing.
Between too many kids in the, without seat
belts, without the s- without the car seat.
No one realized that a kid fell out. The
drugs in the car. There's a lotta things
going on right now. Okay? Okay.
It's not just one thing.
I understand what you're saying though, sir.
Yeah.
I understand.
But
I just got this car.
Alpha 216 11.
Where's my baby G?
Alpha 216.
Don't do this to me.
Hispanic unit within.
726.
Or any time during questioning, you can if
foreign attorney won't be appointed to
represent you. If at any time you wish to
stop talking or have any attorney present,
all questioning will stop at your request. Do
you understand these rights?
With these rights in mind, are you willing to
talk to me?
I will.
I'm sorry?
Make sense? Yeah.
I said with these rights in mind, are you
willing to talk to me?
I don't know what to say.
No? You don't wanna talk to us?
I would be honest.
Like I said, we're giving you the opportunity
to talk to us. We already know most the
answers. We just wanna talk to you to try to
figure out more stuff.
I don't really-
[beep]
... know what to talk about really.
Like i- it... You... First, you have to say
yes you wanna talk to us, or no you don't
wanna talk to us, or no you don't wanna talk
to us. No, I don't wanna talk to you.
No, you don't wanna talk to us? Okay.
But that mean, that mean I'm going to jail?
What?
I'm going to jail?
Um, right now we're at it's still an
investigation, so we're still doing an
investigation into it. Okay? All right? If
you were to go to jail today, your charges
would be driving with no driver's license.
Okay? Um, I don't know how many suspensions
you've had. Um,
possibly driving under the influence,
narcotics, and also child neglect for having
narcotics in the vehicle
with the children on there. And then also
failure to for due cause to make sure that
those children... Since you're the driver,
you're responsible to make sure that they're
in car seats and they're in seat belts. And
you basically drove off and let one fall out
of the car. So you, so you'd be, you'd be
charged with child neglect.
So I'm going to jail?
Like I said, we're still doing the
investigation. That's why we wanted to talk
to talk to you. So at this time, d- would you
want to talk to us, yes or no?
No.
No, you don't want to talk to us? Okay. All
right.
The mom and her brother are arrested for
child neglect and drugs.
DCF is called, but the mum asks them to
contact her mother, to which the
officer agrees.
At this point, your brother's being placed on
arrest for driving under, um, driving with a
suspended driver's license, felony,
possession of marijuana, and the child
neglect. You're also being placed under
arrest for child neglect and possession of
that Xanax pills, if they turn out to be
Xanax, okay?
The two of you had every
reason or right to either, one, put those
kids in a car seat or make sure they were
properly buckled in, but the two of you
failed.
I mean, you put your children's life in
danger by letting him smoke marijuana and
driving like that.
I did not.
Okay, well-
All right, let me call somebody so they can
come get my kid.
All right, give me, here's the... Right now,
I can't sit with your kids while I still have
to come through Miami. So I did call the
Department of Children and Families.
They are on their way to take possession of
your kids, but if you give me that name, I
will give that name to them, and that would
be someone they could contact to turn the
kids over, because I can't... Miami's what?
How far is Miami from here?
About four hours by now.
Four hour, four or five hours? I can't send
them to McDonald's parking lot with the kids
for four hours, so- Then how am I going to
get out to go get my kids? I have to call
somebody to come get them. All right. So who
do you want me to give this number to, to DCF
for your kids to come get them? My mom.
10-4.
You've got my mom number, right? We do?
Yeah.
Do we... Okay.
We do.
Well, can you call her?
Um, before he leaves, he'll give that to me,
and I'll give it to the D- DCF investigator,
and they will call her, okay? What I'm gonna
do is we're going to take you, we're gonna
place you in the back of that patrol car. I'm
gonna place you in the back of that patrol
car. I'm gonna take your oldest child, put
him in one of these cars, and I'm gonna drive
the car, literally from here to the parking
lot, and get them off the roadway. Um, did
the kids eat this morning? 61-53? Breakfast
or anything? Ma'am, did the kids eat
breakfast or anything?
East 11th North today.
Kids eat.
All right. If I was going to McDonald's to
get them something to eat, does anybody have
any allergies or anything, that they can't
eat? All right, so I'll go to McDonald's and
get them some food. 10-4.
Any investigators should be here in the next
half hour, 45 minutes, okay?
So we step on out, [bell ringing] and they're
gonna walk you over to the other car.
And then, there's a puppy in the car too,
correct?
Yeah, those are my puppy.
All right. Puppies? There's more than one in
there?
There's four of them.
All right. They're gonna go to, we're gonna
turn them over to... [car door closing] I
can't... To our, um, animal control.
Hey, can I pick them up?
Yeah, I'll give him your name. He'll be able
to come pick them up.
Um, can I get my, like 10-4, can I take my
credit card in here, so I can grab my own
cell phone? Yes, we'll grab your credit card.
You want your credit card and your cell phone
out of the car, correct? Yes.
Okay, we'll grab that out of the car for you
before we go.
So I give every- I give you, brother, the
opportunity, do you have anything on your
persons? Because if you have anything on your
persons, I can go get a female deputy to come
and search you. All right? But an induction
of anything into my inmate facility is going
to be a secondary charge. So this is why I
give you a few-
So how am I gonna get my car if it's not
under my name on here?
Well, here's... That- that's the problem. The
car is gonna get towed.
10-4.
It's gonna go to the local tow pound. You
won't be able to get it out until you bring a
valid registration and insurance for the car.
Because if the car is not registered, and the
car is not registered, and the car is not
insured, so you shouldn't be driving this on
the car is not insured, so you shouldn't be
driving this on the roads. Okay?
Okay. All right, it's all right.
So that-
I see everything you guys are doing. It's all
right.
Yeah.
Not everything that we're doing. It's
everything that you, the choices that we've
selected to do today. Okay?
Oh, true.
The mother was charged with neglecting her
child and possessing illegal substances,
[keyboard clicking] and was sentenced to two
years of community control followed by
probation, along with a six-month driver's
license suspension.
Her brother was charged with child neglect
and failure to register the vehicle,
though the latter charges were dropped.
He was sentenced to three years of probation,
180 days in jail, a
drug evaluation, and no contact with the
victims during his supervision.
In the next case, the children didn't fall
out of the car, but what happened was just as
dangerous. It was on, it was on, it was on.
There's no key in it. You fucking serious?
I y- I can pull my key, I can pull my key
out, bro.
Jesus.
On a hot summer day, June 21st, 2024, police
got a call
about a parked car at a Harbor Freight store.
Inside that car were children screaming and
crying.
What is wrong? How dare you leave a child in
here without the air on? Are you seriously?
I literally... It was on.
You're fucking crying, dude.
What do you mean?
When officers got to the parking lot, they
found a terrifying scene.
Two young kids locked inside a parked car
with no air conditioning.
The outside temperature was 92 degrees, and
the children were crying in distress.
Thank you very much. Yep.
[car alarm going off]
Hi, sweetie, are you able to unlock the door?
Are you hot? [car alarm going off]
I literally just walked in. Open this fucking
door right now. What is wrong?
How dare you leave a child in here without
the air on? Are you seriously?
I literally... It was on.
You're fucking crying, dude.
What do you mean? It- it was on.
It's not on, dude.
I did-
There's no key in there.
Dude, I promise you-
Are you serious?
... I promise you it was on. It was on, it
was on, it was on.
There's no key in it.
I- I- I can pull my key-
Are you fucking serious?
I can pull my key out, bro.
Jesus Christ.
Dude, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Dude,
please don't take my kids. I'm so sorry.
What is wrong with you?
Turn the car. Get some AC in here.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry, please.
Are you guys okay?
I'm so sorry, guys. [children crying]
Dude, I've literally been in there for like
five minutes. Please don't take my kids.
Dude.
I'm so sorry.
That is ridiculous, dude. Where's your ID at?
Fine.
You're lucky I didn't smash your window out,
dude.
35 medic to 41, one second.
Oh, my goodness.
Where's your ID at?
I don't know. Can I please just talk to you?
Okay, I'm gonna have the medics look at these
kids. Can you step over here?
Okay, that's fine. Can I please talk to you?
There's two, two of them in there, super hot.
They were crying when I pulled up.
Can I please talk to you?
About what?
16-54. Look, I- I've been doing this a lot,
man. I- I tried to return something.
I... They're- they're having an issue
returning it.
I didn't realize that it was gonna take
years, so please
16-54.
Can I give them a hug?
Just stay back for a second, dude.
Can you come with me?
How long have they been in here?
Like, he won't believe you went
10.
I know, I just-
Oh, it's pretty hot, dude.
Yeah, I, I know. I, I ran in-
It's 10.
I tried to return something-
I tried to come back out. I-
Gardner.
... came and leave my key on and I thought
that I had left it on.
The car was off when I got here. Come over
here.
So far, it's 58 A-
Sit right here
... 49 Rene Avenue, 8649 Rene Avenue.
Caller's dad curves in a white red blue
short. He was turning 50 or so.
Oh, how old?
He does have depression and cancer. Recent
diag-
So, what's goin' on, man?
Currently in his room.
I'm struggling, okay.
And he's throwing up 10 times an hour.
Okay.
I ran inside to return somethin'. They were
asleep, I didn't wanna wake them up.
Mm-hmm.
They have no clue. Been busy all fucking day.
Okay.
I can leave my key on.
Yeah.
And leave the key re- or leave the car
running.
Yeah.
And I had thought I had did that and
apparently I had flicked it back.
They had ran inside, I'd been in there for
five, 10 minutes-
Yeah
... and they're, they were having an issue
returning the item that I had t- or that I
was trying to return. So I was coming back
out here and then I see somebody walking
around my car. I'm like, "What the fuck?"
Yeah.
Like, dude, I promise. It was an honest
mistake. I'm, I'm fucking going through...
I've been doing this shit alone.
Mm-hmm.
A- and they were in there fighting. I, I
fucked up and I realize that, bro.
Yeah?
Real quick, do you have any warrants or
anything like that?
No.
Huh? You have nothin'?
So my under- so my understanding is this, is
that these medics were saying it was
extremely hot in that car. I know, and I've,
I've fucked up man and I'm fucked up.
Please don't-
Yeah?
... take my kids from me. I'm fucked up and I
will never do it again. I promise.
Well, first of all, you need to relax.
I understand it's a stressful situation and
everything, but buddy...
I know I fucked up, man.
Yeah.
So-
I'm so sorry.
So, so r- real quick, look at me.
Realistically, how long were you in there?
Five, 10 minutes, man.
Five, 10 minutes, I promise. Five, 10
minutes.
And also, do you... Okay, five to 10 minutes
in this type of heat with nothing running,
with the-
It wasn't off.
With the windows up in the car.
You understand how hot that gets inside of a
vehicle?
Yes, sir.
Do you understand that it can kill a child
within three or four minutes?
I didn't realize it could get that fast.
Huh?
I didn't realize it was that-
Heat, heatstroke's the real thing, boss.
Where?
No, not right now. No.
She's, she's reaching for me.
Not right now.
Not right now. We're, we're talking to you.
We understand it's stressful, we understand
everything else that's going on. All right?
Where you working?
I'm not right now. I'm doing this shit al- I
don't have help, man. I'm doing this shit
alone. Where you living?
I
stay with a friend that's letting me stay
with her.
Well, okay, right now they're gonna check
your kids, make sure your kids are okay.
Okay.
All right?
This is what I'm gon-... You're just gonna
sit right there, buddy, 'cause I'm not gonna
put you in the back of a car. I'm not doing
that right now.
All right? 'Cause you're talking to me, I'm
talking to you.
But as of right now the medics need to check
your kids out and make sure your kids aren't
hurt. Yes, sir. You're right. Thank you.
'Cause I just want you to know, like,
within three to four minutes they could've
died.
Especially with no water, especially with
nothing.
They had water. They-
But-
... I know, but that's not the point.
How old are they? How old are they?
Uh,
four and... Or five and fucking four.
So a five and four-year-old in a hot car.
I know.
Have a seat. H- have a seat. But you need to
understand, if I have a four-year-old in a
hot car like that, okay, look, listen to me,
they're not gonna think to drink water.
They're not gonna think to do any of that.
All right?
So from the outside looking in, 'cause we've
all dealt with this before,
it could've been very bad.
I'm sorry.
What if nobody called the police and they
died? Then what?
I fucked up, I already know. You don't have
to keep telling me, man.
I fucked up, I fucked up, I fucked up.
10-46.
Yeah, yeah, it's a 8 car vacuum.
10-4.
Where are you guys living?
We were living in Menard but one of my
friends finally
I'm
BR Back Malls.
The man had claimed he was only inside the
store for five minutes, but even that short
time was dangerous. The kids were drenched in
sweat, red-faced and clearly overheated.
Temperatures inside a parked car can rise by
20 degrees in just 10 minutes
even with the windows cracked.
I think they're fine. They're fine.
No, guys, I was about to ask you, are they
fine?
We're trying to cool 'em down and everything.
Yeah.
And, uh, I mean, if, are they going back with
him?
As a, right now, I don't know because it's, I
don't know if I can trust them going back
with him. That's what I'm wondering 'cause
then-
At this point. Yeah. 'Cause he said he was
only in there for-
So...
He said he was only in there for five
minutes.
I said, "Even five minutes," I said, "out in
this heat with your windows up with, with no
A- AC going," I said, "you could've killed
your kids easily."
Yeah. And he said five to 10. I'm not really
sure.
Yeah. I mean, they're sweaty, they're warm.
But I was thinking, I was telling him, they,
I don't think they need to go to the hospital
but if they- Well, I was about to say, I was
about to ask you guys.
If they take them for, for we need to take
them for their safety down there, then that's
fine. I think medically-
Okay
... they're, they're probably okay.
Okay. See, they're medically okay?
Yeah, they're very, like, your face is all,
you saw all the red and sweating and...
Do you want me to go in there and ask them
'cause he's standing, it sounded like he was
at the counter for a while.
Oh.
What, what-
You mean in the store?
Yeah, like, how long he was in there for.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, if you don't mind doing that.
Might be security camera by the, uh-
Well, so..
... by the door too. If he's been in, if...
This is some, this will be my call, like I
said, I'll, I'll talk to you about it too.
If he was in there for more than 10 minutes,
I think they should go get checked medically
too. Yeah. Well, yeah, if it's more than 10
minutes, then uh...
Because this,
because this, he's saying, he told me five to
10, but.
He originally told me five and then now he's
saying five to 10.
So, I'm guessing probably a lot. 'Cause he
said he went in there to exchange, to return
something and he was in there for a while
trying to work on exchanging it.
So,
we all know how that can go.
Right. Alright.
But I'm mainly concerned how is making sure
they're okay.
Like, I don't, like, that's not even mean but
I don't, I don't care about that. Yeah.
Yeah. Like I said, medically, I, I think
they're fine.
They need-
Yeah
... probably honestly need some, like, water
to get all those fluids, um.
It's just me, that's about all you'll hear.
But I just wondered for their safety if they,
we need to take them somewhere, I'm s- more
than willing to do that.
Yeah.
Medically, though, I think they're-
Okay
... obviously hot.
Soon his lie came out. Lying when there are
witnesses never works out well, does it?
[whoosh]
The cashier said 15 plus, at least.
Oh, yeah. They need to go, they need to get
to a doctor, probably get checked in at that
point. So the cashier said 15 plus, at least.
So, at-
Yes, 15 plus, I think they should go get
checked-
Round it down
... by doctors at that point.
It's significant.
Because that's...
Yeah, he's...
No.
Well, his first worry was, uh, "Am I in
trouble?"
Yeah. Why, why are you worried about if
you're in trouble and not your kids?
Right.
You need an exchange when you're taking three
kids in there.
Yeah, exactly.
An exchange.
See, that's, that's about my thoughts, yeah.
Yeah.
And he said, "Well, they have water." I said,
I said, "You think a three and a f- however
old they are, four to six year old or
whatever he said, is going to think about the
drink water?" Yeah.
I'm so sorry. [crying] I just love them.
Where's their mama?
They didn't know.
Okay. Is that why you have temporary custody?
It's hard, man. I'm sorry. I fucked up.
Can I hit my vape?
Yeah.
Can I grab it? It's over there.
What's that?
It's the blue American one.
It's in the cen- in the center. Um,
there's... I ain't gonna lie to you, there's
doobies in there. Oh, no. Those are nothing.
I honestly thought I had left because I
didn't believe it.
You know how some of the older cars, you can
flip them on and pull the key out?
I can flip it on and I can pull the key out.
It wasn't on when I got here.
I know. I realized that as soon as I came
out.
I was the first-
You realize it's probably over 100 degrees in
that car when I pulled up?
I mean, that takes two seconds to kill child-
children those age. You know that, right?
I didn't realize I fucked up. I'm sorry.
Can
I give them a hug please? They were-
They'll be out in a minute.
... very important.
They'll be out in a minute. Just hang out
right here.
How, how long did the... How long did you see
them in there?
Um, well, I got here and I immediately
started walking up to the store, but then I
heard crying and I turned back and sure as,
sure as hell the call was unattended. So
that's when I called 911. Okay.
And about... That was about from the time I
made till-
Okay
... the call to when you guys got here. So,
probably like five minutes by the time I got
here. So, probably like five minutes by the
time I got here. Yeah? Okay.
That's all right.
All right.
Well, I appreciate it.
Thanks for helping us. We're safe because of
ya.
Absolutely. No, thank you. Appreciate it.
I'm so sorry.
I really should have just waited until
tomorrow.
Officers decided to detain him, especially
after learning he may have been smoking
marijuana while responsible for the children.
Huh?
Just don't walk around.
Fucking 92 degrees, dude.
I know. And I went in there... Do you hear
this? I went in there and talked to the
cashier that... She said he was waiting in
line for 15 minutes.
No. Are you fucking serious?
Yeah.
I mean, they were all sweaty and shit, but
uh-
Well, at least they're still sweating.
Oh, yeah.
I know.
Somebody should have woken up yelling.
I'll probably hear there's child
endangerment, dude.
Uh, yeah. And, and so we're trying to figure
out... He's...
I don't know if he's on the phone with your
sergeant or what but
we're trying to figure out where they need to
go, if they need to go, because like-
Children's services?
We don't even-
He doesn't have a mom.
Well, if you're... If you're gonna not charge
him with anything and move on, then we can't
really take his kids away from him.
Oh, I know. That's what I'm saying. Right.
But-
Which I think
But when child endangerment comes in.
... he's not important enough though.
Absolutely.
I mean, medically, they just did their
temperatures. Like their temperature's normal
at this point. Now they've been to the medic.
So, you know, get-
Ah. You didn't take them when they first got
out?
No.
Okay.
They were normal before then.
Yeah, yeah. I understand.
What you guys doing, sir?
Everything on you?
Okay.
Yeah, I'll patch you down for both of you.
Turn around, please.
Am I going to jail?
We're gonna talk about it. I'm gonna detain
you right now, okay?
Okay.
What's going in your pockets?
You mind if I take everything out?
No drugs or anything?
No.
I got weed. That's fine. Weed's legal.
You're not driving with the kids in the car
while you're smoking marijuana, right?
That's right. Okay, sir, I've lived a lot to
get to where I'm at.
I can't tell-
All right, you're gonna have a seat in the
back of my car right now.
Are they okay?
Yeah, they're okay.
We're just detaining you for right now.
It's funny, I actually just was there for a
return the other day. The drug conflict is
why I walked in. Oh, yeah?
The kids weren't in the car were they?
No.
Oh, okay. He was trying to attend to us.
I left, uh, I left her at home by herself.
Where's their mom at right now?
I have no clue.
Do you know her phone number?
No, not right now.
Do they have a grandma?
Grandpa?
Yeah, grandma.
That's close?
Yeah.
Is she able to take care of them?
Are you... Am I going to jail?
Yeah. You're gonna go to jail for child
endangerment, man. Can't leave your kids in
here. You know Grandma's phone number?
Yeah.
All right. Give me, give me a second.
What's your grandma's phone number?
Can I please give them a hug? Because I know
their mom's gonna keep them from me after
this. All right.
Please, just one hug.
What's your grandma's number? Step out real
quick. I'm gonna put you in handcuffs.
Can I please give them a hug before you do
that?
All right, no, please. Turn around. Turn.
You should have thought about all this before
you, you did a dumb step, man.
What do you... I...
You're right,
you're right. It's my fault. I'm sorry.
Those too tight?
Is it hot back here?
Even if it was, I wouldn't tell you because I
fucking deserve it.
All right, have a seat.
Did you get ahold of my mom?
No. I think, uh, they're gonna get dropped
off at Doctors Hospital.
And they're okay?
Yeah, they're okay. But it was just...
We don't have anyone else to take them right
now and then-
Can we take them to my mom's?
No, they're gonna go to the doctor's, make
sure they're all good.
And then, uh, Children's Services is gonna go
there as well.
So we, we have to report on something like
this, man.
It's not like-
I know you do, but still.
It's not like, "Oh, you messed up. Okay,
here's your kids back."
... go do it again. You know,
it's something we, we are required.
Otherwise, I don't, I'm not, I'm not gonna
lose my job over something like this.
I know, I know, and...
So from my understanding, you're, you're
doing a return for this gentleman?
I refused to do a return, because he used
half the product and he must have
communicated that,
that like they, they, they usually would
handle that.
Mm-hmm.
They asked me 'cause I'm a leader on duty,
not just because I served him.
Yeah.
But they asked me, "Can he return it if it's
half empty?" And I was like, "No, I did not
say that he could return it if he used it, I
just said if it was 15..."
Yeah. So real quick, if you don't mind, could
you do a witness statement for me stating
like, like he came in here to return the
product where it was, and like, you don't
have to go into too much detail, but just
like, just give us like a rough estimate time
he was in here. Okay.
Because he's telling us a totally different
time.
I can check the camera.
Then what... Yeah, and if you guys have
camera footage as well.
Yeah, I can check the camera and see when he
came in and he was
right there kind of in camera view, I can go
back-
Yeah, and if you could just give us like a
rough estimate time too, like he was in here
approximately this time trying to do this and
everything else.
Okay. You know, I can, uh, I can just
backtrack on the camera and get you like a
time. Okay.
Uh, yeah.
It doesn't have anything to do with the
return.
Okay.
Yeah, i- i- this is a, this is-
I'm like, "How did I just ruin this guy's
life?"
No, no, this is something totally different.
[laughs] Okay.
Thank you so much.
All right, I'll run it.
The store employee confirmed that the man had
been in the store for more than 27 minutes
and only left when he noticed the police had
arrived.
He was then charged with child endangerment.
The children were taken to the hospital and
later placed under the care of CPS.
It's easy to ask, "How could a parent do
this?" But by the time officers arrive, the
worst has often already happened. Kids left
in hot cars, extreme neglect, drug-related
chaos. What might seem like an overreaction
can be the difference between life and death.
It's rarely black and white. Officers have to
make split-second decisions under intense
pressure. Before we jump into the next story,
don't forget to hit that subscribe button so
you never miss these shocking moments.
95 16.
Fairborn Police Department.
On January 1st, 2024, police in Fairborn,
Ohio responded
to a 911 call that quickly turned into a
nightmare.
A mother had called for help but she gave a
fake name, which immediately raised
suspicions. When officers arrived at the
scene, they found a three-year-old girl in
critical condition inside a filthy,
bug-infested apartment.
Fairborn Police Department.
Holy shit, she's breathing, she's still
breathing. Let's go, let's go.
Upon arriving at the scene, the child's
father told police the mother called him
crying that their daughter was starving then
vanished. He hadn't seen the girl in weeks.
She had already lost one child to CPS in the
past.
Now, their second daughter was fighting for
her life and the mother had gone silent.
Her phone on airplane mode, nowhere to be
found.
So there we go.
So how did you come to find yourself over
here?
She called me and was freaking out,
telling me that my daughter was malnourished
and that she was sorry
and she had to go.
Where would she go?
I have no idea.
You know, her mom lives in Yellow Springs,
um, in the, uh,
the, um,
apartments over there by the horse track.
Is my daughter okay?
Well, she's en route to Children's Hospital
right now.
Do you have an ID on you, partner?
I do.
What is your daughter's name?
[beep]
Okay.
Check that out, also, like...
Where would she be going?
I have no idea. She's-
She has no family around here or-
So,
like I said, her mom lives in Yellow Springs
and, uh,
I don't know where her sister lives anymore.
I know that she's been talking to a lot of
people online.
Can I get a picture of this eventually?
Okay, I'll just give it back to you for now,
so don't...
You got a number? I can send it to you.
Just a screenshot?
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
I'll use my
work phone.
Yeah, um,
she's been talking to a lot of guys online,
she's been-
Ready?
Yeah.
[beep]
Getting AIDS on Destiny all night, said
didn't think this was gonna happen.
[beep]
When's the last time you saw your daughter?
It's been a while. She, um,
had kept telling me that she didn't want me
around her because she had had issues of
being raped when she was a child. And that
because of that, she was uncomfortable with
us being in the same room. Gave me reasons to
why she was asleep every time I came over,
and I haven't seen her in at least two, three
weeks.
Okay, and when you saw her-
I just seen her.
And when you saw her two or three weeks ago,
her, she was in good health or...
She wasn't.
Okay.
As far as I was aware.
And, and
so does she have drug problems or what's
going on?
Um, she smokes pot, but I don't think that's
the cause of it.
Uh, about, I wanna say six months ago, we
split up because her
father died and she
went completely off rails after that.
She stopped cleaning, she stopped taking care
of everything, that led to many arguments.
Um, she had asked me to quit my job two years
prior
and, uh, I listened because she was making
like $1,000 a week.
And, uh, so I told her, you know, because I
knew she was struggling, "Get me
clothes. I will go get a job. I will take
care of everything." And she said, "No, I
want you to stay here." And it kept turning
into fights until I caught her cheating with,
or on me with some people online. And, uh,
she's just been in this, in this spiral. She
hasn't cleaned up the room. The last time
I... [beep]
Uh, but she doesn't clean her own room.
I think the only reason she cleaned that room
is because I told her that it, I'd, I'd
seriously fucking hurt her if I found my
daughter in any kind of condition....
because we lost our first daughter because
she had neglect issues.
And, uh, that was the reason we were allowed
to keep this one.
And, uh-
You lost your first daughter, like she... you
had to put her up for adoption or...
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
CPS took her because we were... I had taken
her to my uncle's and
an old friend of mine that I looked at like a
brother
had his gun on him and he was, uh,
ex-military.
So,
I assumed, you know, everything was fine. I
didn't know he had it on him at the time.
He pulled it out to clean it. I wasn't paying
attention and he shot himself in the knee.
Um-
Okay.
I guess it was a bullet wedged in
where he was trying to dislodge and the
handle cocked forward and stabbed the bullet
in his knee. And because of that,
along with, uh, they said that she had marks
on her back, which I had assumed was from
flailing in her stroller, that, uh, they
needed to take custody.
Okay. Would, would you humor me? I know she
said that her,
her, uh, phone's going on airplane mode, but
can you text her back and say, "Hey, I'm
talking to the police, like, you need to come
back here," or something to that effect?
Thank you. Okay, I'll be right back.
While searching the house, they uncovered a
horrifying case of extreme
neglect and abuse that had been hidden behind
the walls of that home.
29516.
Fairborn Police Department.
Okay.
Fairborn Police.
Which one is it? Left?
B.
This is like the old, the older lady...
Uh, they always come out here and check.
Nobody's answering.
All right, let's go in.
Yeah, we're-
Fairborn Police.
Fairborn Police Department.
305.
This is our fed.
Good.
I'm not gonna call the number back, but older
male answered the phone-
Oh fuck.
... and said that he has no idea who-
Oh
... Ariella is and no one needs his phone.
However-
Oh my, oh
... this is the phone number that came up on
the 911.
Oh, goddamn
it. Motherfucker.
Fairborn Police.
Oh, fuck.
305, she was on Wallace.
I'll go.
When she called according to the
geo verify.
Holy shit, she's breathing.
Let's go, let's go.
She's still breathing.
Get a light.
Ah.
Right here, yeah, she's still breathing. I'll
get out of your way, sorry.
Yeah, I'm getting out of the way.
Holy cow.
I'd say just pick up and let's go.
Yeah.
Yeah. What are these fucking bugs here?
Hmm?
Okay.
Oh, fuck.
295.
Oh my God.
Does anyone live here?
What the...
Let's get the fuck out of here.
We haven't even got that far.
Uh, let's get pictures started. I'm going to
call Johnny.
God...
Fairborn Police, if you're here, make
yourself known.
Hey, can you and one of your guys respond
down here?
We found this kid barely alive.
Medics are rushing, uh, the kid to the
hospital.
Um,
yep, yep, we're finishing up trying to clear
this place, but you're definitely gonna want
to clear this place, but you're definitely
gonna want to be down here.
All right, thanks. Bye.
Yeah, I think Zach ripped that one off the
end so...
There was a call,
not here and then they called back there was
a guy. Did you guys hear that part of it?
Yeah.
I was... once I saw the kid I thought he was
zoned out.
So, the lady who called obviously isn't here.
They called the number back and a guy
answered and said he has no idea who- 305.
Good.
We have a Radia
Jasmin
listed as of September 8th
He straight ripped that door. [sirens
blaring]
Paramedics rushed the girl to the hospital.
Moments later, police located the mother,
26-year-old Ravia.
She was quiet, almost numb, as officers
arrested her.
The door's kind of ajar. I'm like, "Oh, they
said there's a kid in there. Nobody's
answering. Let's go in."
Mm-hmm.
We go in. Find the kid,
maybe
two, three, emaciated-
Mm-hmm
... covered in bites.
We thought
she or he we-
Mm-hmm
... was dead on the floor.
Mm-hmm.
But
was barely breathing.
Medic scooped her up,
ran to the hospital.
Okay.
This is what we have.
Who lives here?
That's what we're working on. So far as going
down to the apartment complex.
Uh, right now they said Radia, or something
like that.
It's like a pretty foreign... Just... But I
don't know.
Yeah.
This, this is her apartment? This would be-
Supposedly, that's what we're trying to
determine.
Okay. And that's where she placed the call?
Ma'am-
Again, yes. Um, but it sounds like a male
came back on the line the second
time or something like that.
I... Ronnie Day Jr., nothing with Radia in
there.
Um,
so that's what they're trying to determine is
who, who belongs here and who called us.
Okay.
Um, but we got pictures, and obviously I
called out code enforcement, so...
Okay.
Um, but yeah, if you guys wanna... I don't
know if you want to look through there.
I might have booties if you want 'em.
All right. I guess so.
And it was the back,
back bedroom there with the pink shelf. The
one with, the one with the door ripped off.
Mm-hmm.
That's... Yeah.
You were live when you finished?
Yes, yes. Yeah.
Uh, it's all
... over the wall.
Um, so...
I'm gonna,
I'm gonna grab some boo- booties before I go
in there.
All right. You have 10-15?
Huh?
You got the nice shoes.
Yeah.
I don't know if you heard the... Any...
Um, so basically we showed up here because
somebody said they found a two or
three-year-old breathing, hard,
hard to breathe-
At around
10 AM
my ex-fiance called me to tell me my child,
in her care, was bleeding and unconscious-
Uh, B?
... along the same-
B?
Along the... Saying she was leaving and she
was sorry.
I left from my uncle's house to
rush over
after telling her to calm down, only to
receive a message saying
she was putting her phone in airplane mode
and running off, and that she was sorry.
And to get my things from the apartment.
I arrived at the police outside her door,
only to find that she was gone and my child
was taken to the hospital.
Gotcha. Well, I appreciate that, man.
Well, so-
Well, right now we're trying to figure out a
whole bunch of things, right? A whole bunch
of things, right? A whole bunch of details.
Um... Do you mind if I sit? My back is
killing me. Um, what'd you, what do you want?
Just sit down. [laughs]
You can have a-
We're, we're-
... seat in the back of the-
Yeah, we're gonna ha... You can have a seat
in the back of my car. Um...
Are you guys taking me?
What's that?
Uh, yeah, we are. Okay?
Okay.
So, let's-
Can I take my stuff down then, please?
I'll, I'll take care of that. Let's, uh,
let's walk in the front of my car, all right?
Okay, just... Right here is good. Um, if you
wanna face my car, you don't have, just put
your hands out to your sides.
Nothing, nothing on your, uh,
in your pockets at all.
No shoes.
No pockets. You have, um,
just underwear underneath your sweats?
Just not underwear.
Just your sweats? Okay. Oh, perfect. [police
radio] All right.
Go ahead and put your palms together behind
your back.
322.
Tell me how, tell me how to say your name one
more time?
Ravia.
Ravia? Okay. Ravia, my name is Ryan Rick. I'm
a detective.
Uh, and I am the detective that's gonna be
handling this case.
Can you come home now?
I'm sorry?
I,
I can't.
How is your family now?
I, I can't. Um, it's gonna be a little bit,
so right now, um, you're gonna be taken to
the Fairborn Police Department. Uh, there's
some, some administrative things that we have
to do there. Uh, take a picture and some,
some fingerprints.
But I'm gonna be down to talk to you, uh,
soon. Okay?
Okay.
All right.
We'll work through it.
But I don't know what for it.
So I, I can't, I can't give you an answer
like that only because I don't know.
Um, but...
Okay. All right, very good. Again, I will be
down to talk to you, uh, in just a little
while. All right? Okay.
These aren't too tight, are they?
No, they're fine.
Okay. Let's go around to the passenger side
here.
And have a seat. What's this fella's name
back here?
Travis.
Can you please tell him that that stuff right
there needs to go to my kid's dad?
Okay.
The one that was over here earlier.
Just, just hang out right there, man. I'll be
right with you.
Are you gonna turn around?
Yeah. Yeah.
We need to talk to her.
Hey, just give me a second.
All right.
Love you, Lana.
Is there any way you could cuff me in the
front? I have spinal problems and this really
hurts. Yeah.
[laughs]
Yeah, I can do that. Just, uh, can you turn-
This will hold your
Can you turn-
... for me. Just turn
this.
Uh, let's see here.
Uh,
hang on a second. There we go.
All right, just, uh,
just like that.
Yes.
All right.
[dominant music] Ravia faced charges for
assault, child endangerment and abuse.
She pleaded guilty and was sentenced to nine
years behind bars on July 23rd,
2024. No bond was set as she started her
prison time right away.
The next case will shake you to the core as
two adults were unconscious, possibly dying.
And somewhere inside the same house, there
was a child alone.
Hello? Wayne County.
We're good now.
Right there's good. Start CPR.
Start CPR. I've never done it.
How do you...
It was just after midnight on November 5th,
2023 when a chilling
911 call came in. A woman's voice, shaken and
urgent, reported two people
had overdosed inside a home and there was a
child still in the house.
No one knew if the child was safe. Within
minutes, officers were racing to the scene,
unsure of what they are about to walk into.
And then we'll use this on him.
Just spray it once and then it's done?
Yeah.
Ooh. I'm really confused. [breathes heavily]
Perfect. I know.
Excuse me.
Oh.
When officers arrived, they found a woman
standing at the door.
Her hands shaking, eyes wide with fear.
Inside the home, chaos waited. Two people had
overdosed.
One of them was completely still, not moving,
not breathing.
Hi.
I'm dead.
What's going on? Hello? Wayne County.
Can you repeat
the address?
Yes, they're there. Uh, they're here.
I'll respond.
All right. Both of them?
All right. Thank you. Yes.
What's going on?
[screams]
I'm sorry. I'm just trying to swallow.
Are you okay?
[coughs]
What's going on? Are you- You too or no? Are
you okay?
I took a little bit, like, I'm just a little
bit nervous. So I didn't tell you that way.
Took a little bit of what?
Okay.
You know how to work these, right?
I usually just pass out. But I am a little
dizzy.
Just spray in the nose.
It's the same thing as when we were at the
academy.
You just press that, put one in one nostril
and do...
Ooh.
In both?
No, only in one. And then we'll use this on
him.
Just spray it once and then it's done?
Yep, just over his, one point.
Rolling him over.
Sorry. This isn't good.
Can we get him in a bedroom or something?
Because I got an ambulance.
In the bedroom, yeah.
Can you tell me what this guy's name is?
Uh, the guy? Yeah.
Oh. Fuck.
No, not hurt me.
Him? Oh, is she okay?
We have to put a shot in him.
Oh. Where is he? Where is he?
Okay. I
don't see him. I don't see him.
No, I can get the one,
on her.
Get him out of here.
All right. Do you need to do anything to me?
I know we're focused on them.
Yeah, of course, my dress. I haven't even
opened that.
They stopped breathing. Let's take you
around. Hey, come on in.
Got two right here. I don't know if you
wanna-
Good lord.
Did you want us to get one out?
Tell them we're working two codes.
CPR that one.
Okay. Do you want us to pull one out, is what
I'm asking?
Pull that one, out that one. Start CPR on
her.
I'm sorry. I don't need to do you all.
No, you're good. You're good.
We administered one of both so far.
Okay. You guys have more?
No, about my way here.
You ready?
We have troopers coming in. Oh,
we're good now.
Right there's good. Start CPR.
Start CPR. I've never done it.
How do you...
Just hang and look at him. There you go.
Can you get another Narcan charge?
Yep, just did.
Do you know how to use this?
I can probably figure it out. Attach this
around her neck.
I don't know if I'm doing it right. This is
my first time.
You're doing great.
Keep it up.
This thing goes in here.
Something like that?
Yep. Pull it out and it should look like
this. Nice.
Narcan.
Hey,
can we get a Narcan?
Want me to hold for a second?
Hold for a second.
Adapt mode. Pull red handle to reveal pads.
Here we go.
Ready?
Look at pictures on pads.
Apply pads to bare skin exactly as shown in
the pictures.
All right, you got scissors?
Press pads firmly.
Anybody got scissors? I don't know.
Wasn't that cheap though.
Two here.
Pull red handle to reveal pads.
Look at pictures on pads.
Yeah, thank you.
Apply pads to bare skin exactly as shown in
the pictures.
Anybody else?
Yep.
Press pads firmly.
Did we check for anybody else in here besides
these two?
The other girl really had some.
We have a girl and we have a child.
Provide chest compressions to the beat.
We got a pulse.
Got a pulse?
Yep, we have a pulse.
One hand should be inside the other hand.
Is that good enough?
The other hand should be on top of first
hand.
Yo, Micah, I've got a pulse over here.
Press down hard.
How about over there?
At least two inches.
You got a pulse still?
Yep.
Nice.
She's, she's finally breathing now. That's
good.
There we go.
Hey, working.
Continue with the patient.
Hey.
Hi. There we go. Let's get your head up. Oh,
there we go.
Hey, can you talk to me?
Remember to push hard.
Hey.
I'm gonna sneak behind you real quick. Get a
board.
What's your name?
All right, well...
We're good for now.
Got that? [laughs] All right.
Oh, Lord.
I got more Narcan.
Take another dose for this guy.
You want me to do it?
Yeah. Don't worry. I just kinda...
Got it?
Here it is.
Okay. Ready? Go for it.
There was a kid too.
Where did that
She's
in my apartment next door.
Okay. Is anyone with her?
Yes.
We gotta keep an eye out.
My girlfriend is with her.
Okay, good.
Okay. She said she did too. Yeah.
Yeah. She did. So I'm gonna say if she goes
out...
And he went up too.
Yeah. Oh, gosh.
This is...
Yeah. It's...
You're, you're going to jail tonight.
He's, he's not here. He's on the phone with
her right now.
Yeah.
I just didn't want...
... the kid. [coughs]
Okay.
You're fine.
I don't know what happened.
Granted, she kind of should see this, so
she's down to sh-
Copy.
The kid doesn't need to see this.
Yeah, no, no, I agree.
No.
Kid was the one that met me at the door.
Whose,
whose kid is this? Their-
He is not here.
No.
So who's the mom?
The mom, the mom is Riley. The mom and the
child are next door.
Which is next door?
They are my clients, yes.
Okay.
Riley is identified as the mother of the
child in the apartment.
She explains that people had taken something
that tasted weird, and Amber got dizzy then
passed out.
Question for ya, what are their names?
I don't know her last name. Amber...
First, so first name's Amber?
Yeah, and then-
What's the dude's name?
Gates and Baldwin.
Okay, so we got that one right. Hm. And, and,
uh, whose is Amber? Is this girlfriend?
No, she's a friend of ours.
Okay. Where is, uh,
where does she live?
Around here somewhere.
Okay, so Amber from around here. Do you have
a phone number for her?
Okay.
All right, who's talking about getting
That one.
No, you keep walking. You don't need to talk.
Okay.
Ooh,
I'm really confused.
I know you are. Easy.
[sighs] .
Just remember not to do drugs.
[coughs]
[laughs] What's your first name?
Amber.
Amber? Last name?
Hollister.
Amber, how old are you? I'm sorry.
Um, I don't know. [laughs]
Honey, what's your last name?
Leagert.
Uh, they have it, I think.
I have no idea where I am.
Okay, Madison's bag?
Take a couple steps towards me.
Where's my straw?
The, the deputy's going to grab it.
Okay.
Yeah, I'll get it.
Your date of birth, your birthday.
June 30.
Okay.
What year?
Uh, 2002.
9/30/2002. All right.
All right, thank you.
Make sure you got your ID, sir.
We got a middle initial, Amber?
What?
Do you know what your middle initial is?
R.
R? Okay. We gotta bring them on Medica...
Vehicle back to the accident.
All right, that dude gone?
They're ambulating.
Thank you guys so much.
Thank you.
All right.
Electrode tray connection.
Good luck. Nice to meet all y'all. What's
your name? Riley Hervers.
We were
all drinking a little bit.
Okay.
And then they left. I, I wasn't aware.
I was in the other room trying to put my son
to sleep.
Yeah.
As you can see, he's still freaking awake.
Well, obviously now. I got all the flashing
lights and people running around, so yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um,
so yeah, so they left. I didn't
know what, like, why they left or anything
until they got back.
Okay.
And, um,
they said it tasted weird or whatever.
[alarm blaring] So I tried, I just put it in
my mouth to try some, um...
Just, just like a little bit?
Some of what? Yeah. I, yeah, I put it-
On the end of like the little or tip of your
finger or something?
I put it on, yeah, I put like a little bit on
my finger to try it, and it did-
What was it?
It fucking, it didn't taste right. She got up
and
she said she felt dizzy and went into the
bathroom.
Um, I don't know if she threw up, but I did
see a little bit.
There was something on her shirt, yes.
Yeah, it just, ugh.
Okay.
Is that why the water was running?
[coughs]
She, she turned the water on or something?
It don't matter, so.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
Probably poured something on them.
[coughs]
I remember hearing him try to wake her up.
I got up like five minutes later to go check
on them, and they were just both
passed out.
Unfortunately, it's raining. You okay if we
just get a statement from you quick?
Yeah.
About what happened?
All right. You wanna start that?
Yeah. You're okay with the kid in there for
now?
Yeah. Let me just check on him.
Yeah, check on him. Make sure they're okay
watching for, like, 10 minutes and then...
Can I use the bathroom real quick? Do I have
to pay you? Oh, it's okay. I'll just come in
with you. All right. She's just cleaning up,
so... No, it's okay. Why don't you just
stay... Are you all right?
Yeah, just keep the door open, okay? Just
stay-
You wanna get checked out by an ambulance?
Yeah, I highly recommend-
What's your name, ma'am?
Ooh, geez. [door creaking]
You wanna get checked out by an ambulance?
Yeah, let's get checked out by EMS, okay?
Yeah, I, yeah, I feel better. I, I can't
leave him. But it's still- Yeah, I, I
definitely-
Oh
... want to get checked out. I just can't
leave him. I don't have anybody to watch him.
Well, I think at the moment...
Well,
let's just make sure you're okay.
Like, let's... Yeah, no, that's fine.
And we'll cross that bridge when the time
comes, okay?
Y- yeah. I mean, I think-
Do you need... Oh, I do actually have to pee.
Can...
You didn't pee yet? Okay.
No, I didn't.
Yeah, just...
Yeah, could you open a crack?
Yeah, yeah. A detective on scene expresses
concern that Riley may also be
under the influence and could pass out,
emphasizing the need to find someone to care
for her child. You and your roommate
were drinking. You wanted to drink, correct?
He did. I didn't.
Okay.
I had, like I said, I had like a couple sips,
but that was it. I was trying to put...
I was frustrated, trying to put my son to
sleep.
Yeah.
So,
yeah, I drank a little bit, um.
How you feeling right now?
Are you feeling sick anymore or...
I don't feel sick.
Okay.
I just, my vision's a little... I'm a little
slow.
Which is what happened with them, right?
Okay.
I think, yeah, I think so. I wasn't really
around them.
Like, I walked in and they were passed out.
But you said you tried it, right?
T- yes. I just tried a little bit on my
finger because they said it tasted weird.
Yeah.
So I just try a little bit of it, and then,
like,
five to 10 minutes later, I kind of started
getting a little
dizzier, T- like, I feel like I'm tipsy.
Like, that's it.
Yeah.
Like, I just feel like I'm tipsy right now.
So I don't know what-
Yeah.
... was put in this or whatever.
But, and then, yeah, of course, I got sick
and
just threw up a little bit in there, but I
feel better now.
All right, what's your first name?
Riley.
Or Ryle or...
Um, Riley, so my, I'm Detective Roger
LeClaire.
I'm the, the covering the road supervisor for
the sheriff's office,
uh, tonight. So, um,
one, forgive my appearance. I don't dress in
a regular uniform on day-to-day basis, okay?
So that's why I'm in regular plain clothes.
But who were we gonna call to come t-
... take care of your kid for the evening.
I don't think I-
We have to call somebody. Right now you're
dozing off with me, just talking to me.
So to be honest with you, I'm a little
nervous about you, whatever that was,
affecting you and your breathing and possibly
passing out yourself.
So we gotta take the ch- child into
consideration.
So we have to bring, get that kid to someone
that can care for the kid overnight.
What about Christopher?
Okay?
He's out of town. I think-
Out of town where, then?
I'm not 100% sure. He's been traveling with,
um, carnivals and
stuff, like doing like food and stuff, so...
Okay. All right, we got... Get somebody. Uh,
aunt, great aunt, grandma, grandpa.
I don't care who. So these people that were
here,
y- you said you don't, you don't know them
real well?
Hm.
No. The
dude's my temporary, like, roommate.
Okay.
Um, and then they-
And do you know his name?
Yeah.
What is it?
Gates Mboku. It starts with an M. I don't
really know how to,
um, spell it. So your roommate wanted a
drink.
So- And, and the cocaine, I guess. But I
didn't know until I
got back. And I didn't even really want to do
anything, but they said it
tasted weird. And
I don't know, I just had a, a feeling. Like,
I probably shouldn't have taken it, but
I just had like a feeling and I just wanted
to try it too.
And then, yeah, it did definitely taste
weird. All right.
Let me go hang this up.
Riley, where's all the packaging that was
being used?
Packaging?
That they used to, they carried the stuff in.
The coke.
Coke? Uh, there was like a cap- a little
bitty capsule.
It might still be on the counter.
Yeah, it's next to the oven.
So they're taking... So were you doing pills
and they're crushing them up? Or...
No, I think it was... I, I don't know. I
didn't watch any of it happen.
I just, I didn't-
Well, what did you do?
It was on like a little mirror and I, um-
Put your finger on the mirror?
Yeah, it was right by-
So where's that mirror?
It's in the, um, the drawer.
It's next to the oven. If you're standing in
front of the oven-
Oh, okay. So that's all in the kitchen, too?
Yeah. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay, all right. And put him there.
All right. I got to, um, call his dad.
I'm gonna close the door. Watch your knees.
Okay. Can you call your mom?
They wanna, they wanna take me and like check
me out to make sure I'm okay.
Who's on their way? Uh, his, um, his grandma.
Hello?
Sorry, I don't know your name. [laughs] Am I
able to run in and make him a bag
for, like an overnight bag?
No, just because there's gonna be- Yeah,
yeah, yeah. No, when the time comes. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. No, we'll... I'll help you out.
We'll- All right. Thank you. So they're not
letting you out the car?
No, just because they're still in there.
So are you being detained?
N-
no, I don't think so. Am I being detained? As
of right now, yes, 'cause we're...
And we're still waiting on EMS, don't forget.
Okay.
So, like, right now you're basically our
responsibility because
of the situation at hand. I get it. So,
yeah. I just, I know I made the r- I hope I
made the right decision.
Honey, yes you did. Yes. You potentially just
saved both of their lives.
She made the right decision.
Yeah.
It's okay.
Yeah, I, I definitely feel bad about it, even
though I didn't really know what was going
on and everything. No, it's okay. I... You
made the right decision.
I mean, if you didn't call, who knows where
they'd be right now. Right, right, right.
And one of the only reasons I did call was
because
the male, um, has been through this same
experience
before. Like, I don't- With you? Like- No,
no, no, no, no. Oh, okay.
Someone else. It was Ham- when actually he
like woke up in the
hospital the next morning because one of his
friends gave him- You
said Amber fell on the ground?
If you wanna hop out, they're here.
Unless you're gonna follow someone.
Yeah, but I can hang out.
Yeah. If you wanna just come see them quick,
have them check you out in the ambulance.
Probably just be easier.
Okay.
Um.
I can-
Sorry. Yeah, we, uh-
What's, what's going on?
So, um, we, um, we came here for two other
people.
Unresponsive on the floor, overdoses.
We got the one girl back, but the, um,
the male, they gave him like five shots and
was still agonal breathing and they got him
out of here. But what she's telling me is,
um, uh, is, is all she did was, was she took
her finger, she, uh, touched the powder
and um, uh, she just wanted to taste it.
I'm gonna need you to stay awake for me.
I'm trying, man. I really am.
I know you're trying. We don't know what it
was.
You are gonna go, right? You're gonna go to
the hospital, get checked out?
No one wants to find you dead later, right?
Yes. Yes.
That's the last thing you need for your kid,
right?
I know, I know. Yeah, I'm totally fine with
it. That was the reason I called.
Okay.
Riley is taken to the hospital while
neighbors watch her child until the
grandmother arrives. Officers reassure her
that no one is in trouble, but due to the
child's presence during the overdose, a child
endangerment report must be filed.
I got red cross right by my door. Okay.
So I have your boyfriend's number that's
on... You're on the phone with him? I'm sorry
to interrupt. So
we're gonna be bringing you to the hospital
almost immediately.
Is it okay
if it's okay with them that your neighbors
watch your kid until whoever shows up?
Yeah, that's fine. Okay. I just have to pack
a bag for him.
Like, we don't have anything at our house.
Okay.
Where is his stuff in your apartment?
When grandma comes, why can't grandma go in
the apartment and pack up the shit?
She doesn't know where anything is. I mean, I
could try.
She'll figure it out though. She's a grandma,
right?
Yeah, I guess.
I mean,
how hard is it, right? Some diapers, some
clothes, throw it in a bag and call it good.
I mean, they're, they're all in this room. Is
it okay if you guys watch the kid until the
grandma comes? Yeah.
Okay. Because she's gonna be going to the
hospital.
... pretty urgent. So,
I just wanna make sure it's okay with you
guys.
Yeah.
And I'm, I gotta get in contact with the
woman.
But,
um-
Why are you asking if I can take care of him?
We don't know-
Are there any families coming to get him?
No, he just really needs a diaper change. So
bad.
Okay, yeah. We're trying to figure out right
now, like a diaper bag situation.
I'm not sure if you'd be willing to change
his diaper or what, but I-
We don't have
have
a changing table.
I no idea what you guys are going to do.
Do you know if his mama's coming?
Yeah. But you guys are great people for doing
this.
Oh, thank you so much. I wish I was there.
I know, he doesn't deserve to go through it.
So...
Hey, Riley.
Hey.
How's it going? Can we talk to you?
Yeah.
How's, how's everybody doing?
We're good.
Everybody's alive?
Yes [laughs] . Yeah, it's crazy.
That's good.
Everybody's alive [laughs] .
What's up, bud? So, he said Gates is coming
back?
Yeah, he is.
Okay.
Did you... You tested what was in there?
Did you, um-
[sighs] So, as far as the drugs go, it's not
something where we're gonna
charge anybody with it.
Well, I just wanted to know what was in
there.
Even if we wanted to-
I, I-
No, because-
... you can't tell me?
Not... So, here's the, here's the thing.
When, uh, when, whenever we do these tests
for them, it's like a stupid amount of money
anymore. Oh [laughs] .
So, you know, it's, that's, you know-
Oh.
And-
Because they tested me at the hospital and I,
it only um, cocaine and
marijuana came up in my system. And they told
Gates at the hospital that he was definitely
like, laced with something.
Yeah.
But it didn't show up in my system.
Well, you know when they-
But I, I don't know because she tested me
very, like later after I showed up and
stuff.
Well so, so most... So whenever they do take
the final splice of that it's, it's, it's not
always a perfect mix, right? So, he could
have a bull... So, I, um, all you guys are
doing with... Well, what they were doing like
was lines. Like, I'm like, it, it could've
been a little bit. I, yeah, I didn't... I put
some in my mouth.
No, no, no. Hold on, hold on.
I didn't even... I just didn't know if that
was a different...
Because I didn't snort any, I put some in my
mouth is what I was trying to say.
Okay. Looks like you're trying to be
Superman.
[laughs] Jesus Christ.
But yeah, I probably wouldn't touch it
anymore, obviously, right?
If I-
Yes, of course [laughs] .
If I scared the crap out of you. You go in
there and see your friends on the ground.
Yes [laughs] . Of course. I'm sure he had a
good night with grandma either way, so- Yeah,
he had a good night with grandma either way,
so- Yeah, he did. He had a great night with
his grandma. He definitely did. Did, did they
keep you there all night or did you come home
in the morning? No, I, yeah. They didn't keep
me there all night. I came back. Yeah, he's
me there all night. I came back. Yeah, he's i
n the morning? No, I, yeah. They didn't keep
me there all night. I came back. Yeah, he's
in the morning? No, I, yeah. They didn't keep
me there all night. I came back. Yeah, he's i
n the morning? No, I, yeah. They didn't keep
me there all night. I came back. Yeah, he's
in Penfield. He just got his food. He got
Mexican... Oh, he probably went to that Monte
Alban's. Yeah, yeah, so- So, that's not too
far. It's like a 10-minute drive from here.
So yeah, he'll probably be here in like, 20
minutes maybe. Okay. All right, sounds good.
I don't know if I was going to take too long
or not. We'll, uh... No one's in trouble for
like, the drugs and stuff like that, right?
You, you guys are, you went through a
traumatic experience. We're not doing
anything with that. Yeah.
All right?
Yeah.
So, I just wanted to let you guys know that.
Because that f- what of us...
Um, I'm assuming that you thought it was
coke, I'm guessing.
Yeah.
Probably, right? Yeah, so...
Here's what we got to do though. Because, and
again, I'm gonna work with you guys.
I, I just, I want you to listen to me, okay?
Okay.
So, because there was a child here, we do
have to do, we do have to,
we have to do what's an endangerment. That's
why CPS was here.
Okay.
So what I want to do tonight is I want to
get, I want, hi, hi, I want to get you what's
taken care of. And then uh, you, we're gonna
have to try to do like, an appointment or
something. Because I'm, I'm not gonna take
your child with us. But it's something that
we have to do. This isn't a... This really
isn't an option.
If it was, maybe we'd go a different way but
we don't really have a choice with this
one. Which would help, which is, which is why
I wanted you to eat first.
So, at least you get that and at least I get
that in there, so...
And obviously, we'll have to give a little to
Amber at some point too.
It's just an A misdemeanor and normally they
don't really do anything with them anyways,
so... But it is something we have to go
through.
We'll, we'll bring you down tonight, get that
taken care of and then you don't gotta worry
about it. And then, I don't know if you can
get someone,
someone tomorrow
maybe?
Maybe watch him?
Or if, even if you want to, we can meet you
down there because you have a
car?
Yeah, that's my other driver.
Okay, so... Do you have anything you need to
bring?
Obviously, you probably want your phone and
wallet, right?
Mm-hmm.
Got anything else, or... Probably gonna-
I was just, yeah, she's got stuff from
Hey, hey.
Yeah, no. If you wanna, wanna throw that
away.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, we're, we're coming off work,
we're gonna follow you around like
a bunch of creepers,
but...
Hey, hey.
Why are you yelling at me?
I didn't do anything.
No, just ditch whatever you don't want to
bring.
My toys.
He's afraid you're gonna steal his toys.
Yeah.
Don't need to bring your money, right?
[laughs]
Look.
Yeah, definitely leave that there.
He's got a lot of toys. The most of any kid
I've seen.
The woman was charged with acting in a manner
injurious to a child less than
17.
Well, if there is one thing we've learned
from these cases, it's that no matter how
unpredictable life gets, law enforcement is
always on their front lines facing the
unimaginable. From shocking moments of
neglect to life-altering decisions, these
stories show just how quickly things can
spiral out of control.
If you found these stories as eye-opening as
I did, make sure to like, subscribe and hit
that notification bell so you never miss
another intense case like this.
Stay tuned, we have got plenty more
unbelievable stories coming your way.